{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157725341","data":{"timestamp":" 947157725341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_peyake_peyake-yenake-pazaba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" peyake"," userResponse":" peyake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157732680","data":{"timestamp":" 947157732680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_limame_fobenu-limame-yujaya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" limame"," userResponse":" limame"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157738422","data":{"timestamp":" 947157738422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" ravojo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157744845","data":{"timestamp":" 947157744845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" rutiza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157759439","data":{"timestamp":" 947157759439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pumise_dopufa-pumise-lorewi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pumise"," userResponse":" dopufa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157766486","data":{"timestamp":" 947157766486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pumise_dopufa-pumise-lorewi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pumise"," userResponse":" pumise"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157771864","data":{"timestamp":" 947157771864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rinoke_rinoke-limame-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rinoke"," userResponse":" rinoke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157777327","data":{"timestamp":" 947157777327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuvari_voriza-tuvari-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuvari"," userResponse":" tuvari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157784246","data":{"timestamp":" 947157784246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hufuvo_tunosi-jowoma-hufuvo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hufuvo"," userResponse":" hufuvo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157790783","data":{"timestamp":" 947157790783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mozagu_tunosi-fihulu-mozagu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mozagu"," userResponse":" mozagu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157795643","data":{"timestamp":" 947157795642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walimu_walimu-fobenu-huvufo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walimu"," userResponse":" walimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157803856","data":{"timestamp":" 947157803856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pazaba_tuvari-pazaba-jezipi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pazaba"," userResponse":" pazaba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157809622","data":{"timestamp":" 947157809620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" d78cdde8-6381-45ba-be2b-4177ba32041a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pazaba_tuvari-pazaba-jezipi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157825309","data":{"timestamp":" 947157825308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157826128","data":{"timestamp":" 947157826126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157826340","data":{"timestamp":" 947157826340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157826999","data":{"timestamp":" 947157826998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157827970","data":{"timestamp":" 947157827969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157828750","data":{"timestamp":" 947157828750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157829611","data":{"timestamp":" 947157829610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157829876","data":{"timestamp":" 947157829876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157830558","data":{"timestamp":" 947157830557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157831246","data":{"timestamp":" 947157831245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157836140","data":{"timestamp":" 947157836140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157838541","data":{"timestamp":" 947157838541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157838544","data":{"timestamp":" 947157838544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157839435","data":{"timestamp":" 947157839435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157840143","data":{"timestamp":" 947157840143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157841650","data":{"timestamp":" 947157841650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157842958","data":{"timestamp":" 947157842958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157844615","data":{"timestamp":" 947157844614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157846198","data":{"timestamp":" 947157846197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157847237","data":{"timestamp":" 947157847237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157849141","data":{"timestamp":" 947157849141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157850028","data":{"timestamp":" 947157850028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157851833","data":{"timestamp":" 947157851833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157852824","data":{"timestamp":" 947157852824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157854287","data":{"timestamp":" 947157854286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157855977","data":{"timestamp":" 947157855976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157856286","data":{"timestamp":" 947157856285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157857192","data":{"timestamp":" 947157857191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157858514","data":{"timestamp":" 947157858513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157860195","data":{"timestamp":" 947157860194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157860740","data":{"timestamp":" 947157860740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157861986","data":{"timestamp":" 947157861986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157862754","data":{"timestamp":" 947157862753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157863440","data":{"timestamp":" 947157863440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157864484","data":{"timestamp":" 947157864484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157866514","data":{"timestamp":" 947157866514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157866688","data":{"timestamp":" 947157866688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157867813","data":{"timestamp":" 947157867813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157869640","data":{"timestamp":" 947157869640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157870939","data":{"timestamp":" 947157870938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157871309","data":{"timestamp":" 947157871309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157872326","data":{"timestamp":" 947157872326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157874846","data":{"timestamp":" 947157874846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157874987","data":{"timestamp":" 947157874986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157875958","data":{"timestamp":" 947157875957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157876169","data":{"timestamp":" 947157876169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157876819","data":{"timestamp":" 947157876818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157877355","data":{"timestamp":" 947157877354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157878765","data":{"timestamp":" 947157878764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157879466","data":{"timestamp":" 947157879465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157880259","data":{"timestamp":" 947157880258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157881370","data":{"timestamp":" 947157881369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157881579","data":{"timestamp":" 947157881577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157882169","data":{"timestamp":" 947157882168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157884064","data":{"timestamp":" 947157884064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157884244","data":{"timestamp":" 947157884244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157886083","data":{"timestamp":" 947157886082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157886093","data":{"timestamp":" 947157886092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157886651","data":{"timestamp":" 947157886651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157888091","data":{"timestamp":" 947157888091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157889982","data":{"timestamp":" 947157889982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157891287","data":{"timestamp":" 947157891287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157893140","data":{"timestamp":" 947157893140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157894033","data":{"timestamp":" 947157894033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157895022","data":{"timestamp":" 947157895021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157895725","data":{"timestamp":" 947157895725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157896053","data":{"timestamp":" 947157896053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157897976","data":{"timestamp":" 947157897975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157898566","data":{"timestamp":" 947157898566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157899465","data":{"timestamp":" 947157899464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157900521","data":{"timestamp":" 947157900521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157901091","data":{"timestamp":" 947157901090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157901834","data":{"timestamp":" 947157901833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157902733","data":{"timestamp":" 947157902732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157903277","data":{"timestamp":" 947157903277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157904300","data":{"timestamp":" 947157904300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157905648","data":{"timestamp":" 947157905647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157906667","data":{"timestamp":" 947157906665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157907958","data":{"timestamp":" 947157907957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157909733","data":{"timestamp":" 947157909733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157910673","data":{"timestamp":" 947157910672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157911955","data":{"timestamp":" 947157911955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157914527","data":{"timestamp":" 947157914526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157915147","data":{"timestamp":" 947157915147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157916537","data":{"timestamp":" 947157916536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157918368","data":{"timestamp":" 947157918367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157921242","data":{"timestamp":" 947157921242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157921870","data":{"timestamp":" 947157921869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157922624","data":{"timestamp":" 947157922623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157923617","data":{"timestamp":" 947157923617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157925487","data":{"timestamp":" 947157925487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157927075","data":{"timestamp":" 947157927075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157928034","data":{"timestamp":" 947157928034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157929856","data":{"timestamp":" 947157929856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157931163","data":{"timestamp":" 947157931163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157933752","data":{"timestamp":" 947157933752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157934687","data":{"timestamp":" 947157934686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" START_MAYOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157936374","data":{"timestamp":" 947157936374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157937766","data":{"timestamp":" 947157937766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157939331","data":{"timestamp":" 947157939330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157941920","data":{"timestamp":" 947157941919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157942839","data":{"timestamp":" 947157942838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157943168","data":{"timestamp":" 947157943167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157943876","data":{"timestamp":" 947157943876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157944822","data":{"timestamp":" 947157944822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157945780","data":{"timestamp":" 947157945779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157948871","data":{"timestamp":" 947157948870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157949494","data":{"timestamp":" 947157949494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157950322","data":{"timestamp":" 947157950322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157952094","data":{"timestamp":" 947157952094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157952976","data":{"timestamp":" 947157952976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157953147","data":{"timestamp":" 947157953147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157954246","data":{"timestamp":" 947157954246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157954797","data":{"timestamp":" 947157954796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157956635","data":{"timestamp":" 947157956634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157957201","data":{"timestamp":" 947157957200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157958654","data":{"timestamp":" 947157958653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157959516","data":{"timestamp":" 947157959515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157961019","data":{"timestamp":" 947157961018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157962178","data":{"timestamp":" 947157962177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157962746","data":{"timestamp":" 947157962745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157963425","data":{"timestamp":" 947157963424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157964026","data":{"timestamp":" 947157964025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157964244","data":{"timestamp":" 947157964244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157964848","data":{"timestamp":" 947157964848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157965357","data":{"timestamp":" 947157965356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157968204","data":{"timestamp":" 947157968203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157969630","data":{"timestamp":" 947157969629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157971252","data":{"timestamp":" 947157971252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157972757","data":{"timestamp":" 947157972757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157976441","data":{"timestamp":" 947157976441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOWAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157977414","data":{"timestamp":" 947157977414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157979282","data":{"timestamp":" 947157979281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157980373","data":{"timestamp":" 947157980372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157981048","data":{"timestamp":" 947157981048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157982653","data":{"timestamp":" 947157982653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157984674","data":{"timestamp":" 947157984674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157985609","data":{"timestamp":" 947157985608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157986861","data":{"timestamp":" 947157986860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" START_WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157988571","data":{"timestamp":" 947157988570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157989450","data":{"timestamp":" 947157989450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157990347","data":{"timestamp":" 947157990347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157991341","data":{"timestamp":" 947157991340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157993876","data":{"timestamp":" 947157993875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157994395","data":{"timestamp":" 947157994395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157995183","data":{"timestamp":" 947157995183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157996837","data":{"timestamp":" 947157996837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157997481","data":{"timestamp":" 947157997480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157997685","data":{"timestamp":" 947157997685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947157997899","data":{"timestamp":" 947157997899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158000543","data":{"timestamp":" 947158000543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158001255","data":{"timestamp":" 947158001255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158002548","data":{"timestamp":" 947158002548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158003644","data":{"timestamp":" 947158003644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158004864","data":{"timestamp":" 947158004864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158005824","data":{"timestamp":" 947158005824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158008026","data":{"timestamp":" 947158008025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158009896","data":{"timestamp":" 947158009896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158011221","data":{"timestamp":" 947158011221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158012115","data":{"timestamp":" 947158012115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158012719","data":{"timestamp":" 947158012718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158014674","data":{"timestamp":" 947158014674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158017571","data":{"timestamp":" 947158017570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158018049","data":{"timestamp":" 947158018048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158018668","data":{"timestamp":" 947158018667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158019372","data":{"timestamp":" 947158019371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158019660","data":{"timestamp":" 947158019660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158020200","data":{"timestamp":" 947158020199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158023365","data":{"timestamp":" 947158023365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158024291","data":{"timestamp":" 947158024290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158026483","data":{"timestamp":" 947158026483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158027560","data":{"timestamp":" 947158027560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158028859","data":{"timestamp":" 947158028858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158029815","data":{"timestamp":" 947158029815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158030871","data":{"timestamp":" 947158030871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158031389","data":{"timestamp":" 947158031389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158033440","data":{"timestamp":" 947158033439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158034916","data":{"timestamp":" 947158034916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158035291","data":{"timestamp":" 947158035291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158036061","data":{"timestamp":" 947158036061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158036923","data":{"timestamp":" 947158036922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158037789","data":{"timestamp":" 947158037787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158038599","data":{"timestamp":" 947158038599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158040557","data":{"timestamp":" 947158040557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158041760","data":{"timestamp":" 947158041759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" START_ZILIPITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158043777","data":{"timestamp":" 947158043777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158045606","data":{"timestamp":" 947158045605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158047059","data":{"timestamp":" 947158047059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158047889","data":{"timestamp":" 947158047889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158048812","data":{"timestamp":" 947158048812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158051194","data":{"timestamp":" 947158051194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158052691","data":{"timestamp":" 947158052690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158054399","data":{"timestamp":" 947158054399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158056960","data":{"timestamp":" 947158056960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158058441","data":{"timestamp":" 947158058437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158059016","data":{"timestamp":" 947158059015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158061056","data":{"timestamp":" 947158061055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158061750","data":{"timestamp":" 947158061750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158062365","data":{"timestamp":" 947158062365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158064668","data":{"timestamp":" 947158064667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158065661","data":{"timestamp":" 947158065660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158066288","data":{"timestamp":" 947158066287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158066773","data":{"timestamp":" 947158066772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158067685","data":{"timestamp":" 947158067684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158068577","data":{"timestamp":" 947158068576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158069205","data":{"timestamp":" 947158069204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158069681","data":{"timestamp":" 947158069681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158070804","data":{"timestamp":" 947158070803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158071253","data":{"timestamp":" 947158071253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158072276","data":{"timestamp":" 947158072275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158072890","data":{"timestamp":" 947158072889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158075256","data":{"timestamp":" 947158075255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158076901","data":{"timestamp":" 947158076901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158078756","data":{"timestamp":" 947158078756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158080575","data":{"timestamp":" 947158080575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158081684","data":{"timestamp":" 947158081683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158082992","data":{"timestamp":" 947158082991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158084282","data":{"timestamp":" 947158084282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158085200","data":{"timestamp":" 947158085200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" START_WAPITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158086207","data":{"timestamp":" 947158086207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158087691","data":{"timestamp":" 947158087690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158088770","data":{"timestamp":" 947158088770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158090385","data":{"timestamp":" 947158090384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158091374","data":{"timestamp":" 947158091374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158092460","data":{"timestamp":" 947158092459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158094132","data":{"timestamp":" 947158094131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158095327","data":{"timestamp":" 947158095326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158097904","data":{"timestamp":" 947158097903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158098814","data":{"timestamp":" 947158098813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158099081","data":{"timestamp":" 947158099080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158099954","data":{"timestamp":" 947158099953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158100603","data":{"timestamp":" 947158100602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158101557","data":{"timestamp":" 947158101556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158103761","data":{"timestamp":" 947158103761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158104374","data":{"timestamp":" 947158104373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158106358","data":{"timestamp":" 947158106358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158107728","data":{"timestamp":" 947158107728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158108768","data":{"timestamp":" 947158108768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158111158","data":{"timestamp":" 947158111157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158112094","data":{"timestamp":" 947158112093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" START_NJIANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158113845","data":{"timestamp":" 947158113845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158115655","data":{"timestamp":" 947158115654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158116210","data":{"timestamp":" 947158116210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158117391","data":{"timestamp":" 947158117390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158118280","data":{"timestamp":" 947158118279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158119361","data":{"timestamp":" 947158119360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158120252","data":{"timestamp":" 947158120251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158122066","data":{"timestamp":" 947158122066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158122423","data":{"timestamp":" 947158122423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158124278","data":{"timestamp":" 947158124278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158126380","data":{"timestamp":" 947158126380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" START_MWINDAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158127845","data":{"timestamp":" 947158127844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158130333","data":{"timestamp":" 947158130332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158132245","data":{"timestamp":" 947158132244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158133635","data":{"timestamp":" 947158133635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158135999","data":{"timestamp":" 947158135998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158136691","data":{"timestamp":" 947158136690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158136898","data":{"timestamp":" 947158136897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158137756","data":{"timestamp":" 947158137755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158138588","data":{"timestamp":" 947158138588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158139159","data":{"timestamp":" 947158139158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158139343","data":{"timestamp":" 947158139343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158139870","data":{"timestamp":" 947158139869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158142064","data":{"timestamp":" 947158142064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158146103","data":{"timestamp":" 947158146103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158147198","data":{"timestamp":" 947158147198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158147773","data":{"timestamp":" 947158147773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158148184","data":{"timestamp":" 947158148184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" START_TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158149737","data":{"timestamp":" 947158149736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158151962","data":{"timestamp":" 947158151961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158153380","data":{"timestamp":" 947158153380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" START_MTOTOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158154878","data":{"timestamp":" 947158154878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158156901","data":{"timestamp":" 947158156901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158158159","data":{"timestamp":" 947158158159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158160964","data":{"timestamp":" 947158160963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158162271","data":{"timestamp":" 947158162270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158163220","data":{"timestamp":" 947158163219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158163996","data":{"timestamp":" 947158163995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158164625","data":{"timestamp":" 947158164624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158165192","data":{"timestamp":" 947158165192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158165759","data":{"timestamp":" 947158165759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158167789","data":{"timestamp":" 947158167788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158168384","data":{"timestamp":" 947158168384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158169408","data":{"timestamp":" 947158169407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158171541","data":{"timestamp":" 947158171540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158172427","data":{"timestamp":" 947158172426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158173137","data":{"timestamp":" 947158173136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158174395","data":{"timestamp":" 947158174395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158175919","data":{"timestamp":" 947158175919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158176554","data":{"timestamp":" 947158176553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158178740","data":{"timestamp":" 947158178739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158179832","data":{"timestamp":" 947158179831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158180919","data":{"timestamp":" 947158180918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158181367","data":{"timestamp":" 947158181366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158182017","data":{"timestamp":" 947158182016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158183378","data":{"timestamp":" 947158183377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158184239","data":{"timestamp":" 947158184239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158184787","data":{"timestamp":" 947158184786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158185546","data":{"timestamp":" 947158185545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158187740","data":{"timestamp":" 947158187739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158188676","data":{"timestamp":" 947158188676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158190458","data":{"timestamp":" 947158190457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158191821","data":{"timestamp":" 947158191820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158194367","data":{"timestamp":" 947158194366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158196080","data":{"timestamp":" 947158196079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158198768","data":{"timestamp":" 947158198768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" START_WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158200065","data":{"timestamp":" 947158200065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158201664","data":{"timestamp":" 947158201664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158203695","data":{"timestamp":" 947158203695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158204760","data":{"timestamp":" 947158204760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" START_WATATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158206260","data":{"timestamp":" 947158206260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158208229","data":{"timestamp":" 947158208229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158210428","data":{"timestamp":" 947158210427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158211752","data":{"timestamp":" 947158211751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158214931","data":{"timestamp":" 947158214930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158217291","data":{"timestamp":" 947158217291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158217758","data":{"timestamp":" 947158217757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158218915","data":{"timestamp":" 947158218914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158219972","data":{"timestamp":" 947158219971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158220920","data":{"timestamp":" 947158220919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158223982","data":{"timestamp":" 947158223982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158224948","data":{"timestamp":" 947158224948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158226438","data":{"timestamp":" 947158226437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158228713","data":{"timestamp":" 947158228712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158229008","data":{"timestamp":" 947158229007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" START_WALIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158233028","data":{"timestamp":" 947158233027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158237416","data":{"timestamp":" 947158237415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158238823","data":{"timestamp":" 947158238823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158240647","data":{"timestamp":" 947158240646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158241815","data":{"timestamp":" 947158241815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158244465","data":{"timestamp":" 947158244464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158245670","data":{"timestamp":" 947158245670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158246493","data":{"timestamp":" 947158246492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158248303","data":{"timestamp":" 947158248302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158249032","data":{"timestamp":" 947158249031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158251024","data":{"timestamp":" 947158251023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158252541","data":{"timestamp":" 947158252540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158253663","data":{"timestamp":" 947158253663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158255371","data":{"timestamp":" 947158255371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158256439","data":{"timestamp":" 947158256439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158258094","data":{"timestamp":" 947158258094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158258577","data":{"timestamp":" 947158258577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158260318","data":{"timestamp":" 947158260317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158261318","data":{"timestamp":" 947158261317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158262572","data":{"timestamp":" 947158262570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158263833","data":{"timestamp":" 947158263831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158264239","data":{"timestamp":" 947158264238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158265111","data":{"timestamp":" 947158265110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158265743","data":{"timestamp":" 947158265743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158266568","data":{"timestamp":" 947158266564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158268246","data":{"timestamp":" 947158268245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158268943","data":{"timestamp":" 947158268943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158270806","data":{"timestamp":" 947158270806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158272106","data":{"timestamp":" 947158272106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158272115","data":{"timestamp":" 947158272114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158274287","data":{"timestamp":" 947158274287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158275029","data":{"timestamp":" 947158275028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158278441","data":{"timestamp":" 947158278441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158281021","data":{"timestamp":" 947158281021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158281587","data":{"timestamp":" 947158281586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158283086","data":{"timestamp":" 947158283085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158283849","data":{"timestamp":" 947158283849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158284066","data":{"timestamp":" 947158284065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158284503","data":{"timestamp":" 947158284502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158285412","data":{"timestamp":" 947158285411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158286599","data":{"timestamp":" 947158286599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158287745","data":{"timestamp":" 947158287744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158288500","data":{"timestamp":" 947158288499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158288708","data":{"timestamp":" 947158288707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158289728","data":{"timestamp":" 947158289727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158292092","data":{"timestamp":" 947158292092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" START_WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158293392","data":{"timestamp":" 947158293392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158296369","data":{"timestamp":" 947158296368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158297901","data":{"timestamp":" 947158297900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158298313","data":{"timestamp":" 947158298313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158299856","data":{"timestamp":" 947158299856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158301872","data":{"timestamp":" 947158301871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158304062","data":{"timestamp":" 947158304061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" START_KUCHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158306093","data":{"timestamp":" 947158306092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158307816","data":{"timestamp":" 947158307815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158309604","data":{"timestamp":" 947158309604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158309911","data":{"timestamp":" 947158309911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158312396","data":{"timestamp":" 947158312396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" START_TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158314065","data":{"timestamp":" 947158314064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158315753","data":{"timestamp":" 947158315753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158316801","data":{"timestamp":" 947158316801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158319046","data":{"timestamp":" 947158319046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158320104","data":{"timestamp":" 947158320104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158321904","data":{"timestamp":" 947158321904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158324862","data":{"timestamp":" 947158324862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158326644","data":{"timestamp":" 947158326643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158328261","data":{"timestamp":" 947158328261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158330666","data":{"timestamp":" 947158330666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158331233","data":{"timestamp":" 947158331232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158332024","data":{"timestamp":" 947158332024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158332580","data":{"timestamp":" 947158332579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158333758","data":{"timestamp":" 947158333758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158334733","data":{"timestamp":" 947158334732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158335230","data":{"timestamp":" 947158335230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158336049","data":{"timestamp":" 947158336048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158338373","data":{"timestamp":" 947158338373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158338980","data":{"timestamp":" 947158338980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158340412","data":{"timestamp":" 947158340412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158340422","data":{"timestamp":" 947158340422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158341893","data":{"timestamp":" 947158341892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158342806","data":{"timestamp":" 947158342806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" START_ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158344835","data":{"timestamp":" 947158344835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158345720","data":{"timestamp":" 947158345720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158346150","data":{"timestamp":" 947158346149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" START_WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158346989","data":{"timestamp":" 947158346988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158349359","data":{"timestamp":" 947158349358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158350008","data":{"timestamp":" 947158350007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158350223","data":{"timestamp":" 947158350223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158351252","data":{"timestamp":" 947158351252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158352279","data":{"timestamp":" 947158352279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158353097","data":{"timestamp":" 947158353097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158354286","data":{"timestamp":" 947158354285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158354623","data":{"timestamp":" 947158354623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158355617","data":{"timestamp":" 947158355616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158356277","data":{"timestamp":" 947158356277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158358658","data":{"timestamp":" 947158358657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158359360","data":{"timestamp":" 947158359360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158360163","data":{"timestamp":" 947158360162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158361595","data":{"timestamp":" 947158361595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158364321","data":{"timestamp":" 947158364321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" START_MWINDAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158365475","data":{"timestamp":" 947158365475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158367496","data":{"timestamp":" 947158367495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158370076","data":{"timestamp":" 947158370075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158372872","data":{"timestamp":" 947158372872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" START_WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158374975","data":{"timestamp":" 947158374975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158375324","data":{"timestamp":" 947158375324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158376329","data":{"timestamp":" 947158376328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158377462","data":{"timestamp":" 947158377462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158379570","data":{"timestamp":" 947158379569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158381946","data":{"timestamp":" 947158381946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158383247","data":{"timestamp":" 947158383246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158384326","data":{"timestamp":" 947158384325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158386604","data":{"timestamp":" 947158386604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158387630","data":{"timestamp":" 947158387630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158388946","data":{"timestamp":" 947158388946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158390644","data":{"timestamp":" 947158390644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158392295","data":{"timestamp":" 947158392294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158392819","data":{"timestamp":" 947158392819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158393411","data":{"timestamp":" 947158393411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158395266","data":{"timestamp":" 947158395266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158395662","data":{"timestamp":" 947158395662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158396461","data":{"timestamp":" 947158396461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158399391","data":{"timestamp":" 947158399390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158399824","data":{"timestamp":" 947158399823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158400519","data":{"timestamp":" 947158400519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158401350","data":{"timestamp":" 947158401350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158401971","data":{"timestamp":" 947158401971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158402539","data":{"timestamp":" 947158402539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158403760","data":{"timestamp":" 947158403758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" KUMBARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158407606","data":{"timestamp":" 947158407606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158409510","data":{"timestamp":" 947158409510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158411410","data":{"timestamp":" 947158411410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158411774","data":{"timestamp":" 947158411774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158412883","data":{"timestamp":" 947158412882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158414075","data":{"timestamp":" 947158414074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158416492","data":{"timestamp":" 947158416491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158418540","data":{"timestamp":" 947158418540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158420740","data":{"timestamp":" 947158420739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158422389","data":{"timestamp":" 947158422388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158424230","data":{"timestamp":" 947158424230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158427456","data":{"timestamp":" 947158427455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158431357","data":{"timestamp":" 947158431357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" KUMBARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158434243","data":{"timestamp":" 947158434243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158434718","data":{"timestamp":" 947158434717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158435440","data":{"timestamp":" 947158435439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158436180","data":{"timestamp":" 947158436179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158437230","data":{"timestamp":" 947158437229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158438282","data":{"timestamp":" 947158438281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158438635","data":{"timestamp":" 947158438635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158439433","data":{"timestamp":" 947158439433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158441581","data":{"timestamp":" 947158441580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158442396","data":{"timestamp":" 947158442395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158444264","data":{"timestamp":" 947158444264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158446030","data":{"timestamp":" 947158446030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158447531","data":{"timestamp":" 947158447531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158451432","data":{"timestamp":" 947158451432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158453130","data":{"timestamp":" 947158453130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158454474","data":{"timestamp":" 947158454474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158455991","data":{"timestamp":" 947158455991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158458344","data":{"timestamp":" 947158458343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158460239","data":{"timestamp":" 947158460239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158461518","data":{"timestamp":" 947158461517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158463231","data":{"timestamp":" 947158463231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158465560","data":{"timestamp":" 947158465559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158466427","data":{"timestamp":" 947158466426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158467632","data":{"timestamp":" 947158467631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" KIFUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158467853","data":{"timestamp":" 947158467852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158468629","data":{"timestamp":" 947158468628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158469516","data":{"timestamp":" 947158469515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158471991","data":{"timestamp":" 947158471990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158472779","data":{"timestamp":" 947158472779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158473997","data":{"timestamp":" 947158473996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158475355","data":{"timestamp":" 947158475354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" KIFUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158476552","data":{"timestamp":" 947158476552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158478466","data":{"timestamp":" 947158478466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158479074","data":{"timestamp":" 947158479073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158481086","data":{"timestamp":" 947158481084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158481211","data":{"timestamp":" 947158481211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 29a90c75-1df2-4b9f-9215-52699a549f90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158497663","data":{"timestamp":" 947158497663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158500376","data":{"timestamp":" 947158500376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158501518","data":{"timestamp":" 947158501518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158502607","data":{"timestamp":" 947158502607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158502820","data":{"timestamp":" 947158502820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158505032","data":{"timestamp":" 947158505032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158506327","data":{"timestamp":" 947158506327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158508532","data":{"timestamp":" 947158508532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158510214","data":{"timestamp":" 947158510213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158512128","data":{"timestamp":" 947158512127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158512825","data":{"timestamp":" 947158512825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158513935","data":{"timestamp":" 947158513935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158515225","data":{"timestamp":" 947158515224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158517067","data":{"timestamp":" 947158517066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158518768","data":{"timestamp":" 947158518767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158519585","data":{"timestamp":" 947158519584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158519788","data":{"timestamp":" 947158519787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158520447","data":{"timestamp":" 947158520446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158521420","data":{"timestamp":" 947158521420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158522203","data":{"timestamp":" 947158522202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158523059","data":{"timestamp":" 947158523059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158523326","data":{"timestamp":" 947158523325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158524008","data":{"timestamp":" 947158524007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158524700","data":{"timestamp":" 947158524699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158527466","data":{"timestamp":" 947158527466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158527659","data":{"timestamp":" 947158527659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158529894","data":{"timestamp":" 947158529894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158530725","data":{"timestamp":" 947158530724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158532669","data":{"timestamp":" 947158532668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158534114","data":{"timestamp":" 947158534114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158535561","data":{"timestamp":" 947158535561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158536724","data":{"timestamp":" 947158536724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158539132","data":{"timestamp":" 947158539131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158540790","data":{"timestamp":" 947158540789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158541339","data":{"timestamp":" 947158541338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158542586","data":{"timestamp":" 947158542586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZAA"," userResponse":" ALIPOZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158543355","data":{"timestamp":" 947158543355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158544046","data":{"timestamp":" 947158544045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158545105","data":{"timestamp":" 947158545104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mara alipozaa mtoto wake alifariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFARIKI"," userResponse":" ALIFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158552488","data":{"timestamp":" 947158552487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158553274","data":{"timestamp":" 947158553273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158554366","data":{"timestamp":" 947158554366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158555976","data":{"timestamp":" 947158555975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158556452","data":{"timestamp":" 947158556452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158558365","data":{"timestamp":" 947158558364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158559364","data":{"timestamp":" 947158559364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158560205","data":{"timestamp":" 947158560205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" START_ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158562074","data":{"timestamp":" 947158562074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158563531","data":{"timestamp":" 947158563531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158565249","data":{"timestamp":" 947158565249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158566793","data":{"timestamp":" 947158566793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158568321","data":{"timestamp":" 947158568321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158568808","data":{"timestamp":" 947158568807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158569593","data":{"timestamp":" 947158569593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158572073","data":{"timestamp":" 947158572073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158574027","data":{"timestamp":" 947158574026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158574162","data":{"timestamp":" 947158574162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158575116","data":{"timestamp":" 947158575115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFILIWA"," userResponse":" KUFILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158575320","data":{"timestamp":" 947158575319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158575970","data":{"timestamp":" 947158575969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158576507","data":{"timestamp":" 947158576506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158577900","data":{"timestamp":" 947158577900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIMFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158578585","data":{"timestamp":" 947158578585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158579374","data":{"timestamp":" 947158579373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158580481","data":{"timestamp":" 947158580480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158580688","data":{"timestamp":" 947158580688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158581280","data":{"timestamp":" 947158581279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uchungu wa kufiliwa na watoto wake ulimfanya tumbili kuruka juu na chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158584012","data":{"timestamp":" 947158584012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158585402","data":{"timestamp":" 947158585402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158586147","data":{"timestamp":" 947158586147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158587770","data":{"timestamp":" 947158587769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158588520","data":{"timestamp":" 947158588520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158590248","data":{"timestamp":" 947158590248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158594022","data":{"timestamp":" 947158594022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158596507","data":{"timestamp":" 947158596507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158597202","data":{"timestamp":" 947158597202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158597280","data":{"timestamp":" 947158597280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158598726","data":{"timestamp":" 947158598726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158600204","data":{"timestamp":" 947158600204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158600759","data":{"timestamp":" 947158600759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" START_AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158602079","data":{"timestamp":" 947158602079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158602664","data":{"timestamp":" 947158602663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158603975","data":{"timestamp":" 947158603975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158605077","data":{"timestamp":" 947158605077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158606572","data":{"timestamp":" 947158606572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158608266","data":{"timestamp":" 947158608266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158609259","data":{"timestamp":" 947158609259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158610643","data":{"timestamp":" 947158610642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158612580","data":{"timestamp":" 947158612576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158613165","data":{"timestamp":" 947158613165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158614061","data":{"timestamp":" 947158614061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158615121","data":{"timestamp":" 947158615121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUKIA"," userResponse":" AKIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158615688","data":{"timestamp":" 947158615688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158616427","data":{"timestamp":" 947158616426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158617329","data":{"timestamp":" 947158617328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158617889","data":{"timestamp":" 947158617889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158618910","data":{"timestamp":" 947158618910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158620260","data":{"timestamp":" 947158620259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPIGA"," userResponse":" AKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158621284","data":{"timestamp":" 947158621284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158622574","data":{"timestamp":" 947158622574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili huyu alikuwa akirukia tawi hili hadi kwenye lingine akipiga mayowe Kwi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158626263","data":{"timestamp":" 947158626262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158628267","data":{"timestamp":" 947158628267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158630082","data":{"timestamp":" 947158630082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158630533","data":{"timestamp":" 947158630533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158631869","data":{"timestamp":" 947158631869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158632869","data":{"timestamp":" 947158632868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158634527","data":{"timestamp":" 947158634526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158636307","data":{"timestamp":" 947158636306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158638113","data":{"timestamp":" 947158638113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158640113","data":{"timestamp":" 947158640112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158641032","data":{"timestamp":" 947158641031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158641366","data":{"timestamp":" 947158641365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158642076","data":{"timestamp":" 947158642075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158643014","data":{"timestamp":" 947158643014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158643974","data":{"timestamp":" 947158643972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alikuwa na huzuni wakati wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158645940","data":{"timestamp":" 947158645940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158648346","data":{"timestamp":" 947158648346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158650544","data":{"timestamp":" 947158650543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" START_ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158652392","data":{"timestamp":" 947158652391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158653883","data":{"timestamp":" 947158653882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158655490","data":{"timestamp":" 947158655489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158656831","data":{"timestamp":" 947158656830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158658699","data":{"timestamp":" 947158658699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158659964","data":{"timestamp":" 947158659964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158660755","data":{"timestamp":" 947158660754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158662282","data":{"timestamp":" 947158662282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158663818","data":{"timestamp":" 947158663818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158665429","data":{"timestamp":" 947158665429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158667925","data":{"timestamp":" 947158667924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158668921","data":{"timestamp":" 947158668921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158669658","data":{"timestamp":" 947158669658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158670420","data":{"timestamp":" 947158670420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158671777","data":{"timestamp":" 947158671776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158673614","data":{"timestamp":" 947158673613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158674178","data":{"timestamp":" 947158674177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158675627","data":{"timestamp":" 947158675627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIMZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158676489","data":{"timestamp":" 947158676487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASWA"," userResponse":" HASWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158677995","data":{"timestamp":" 947158677994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158679159","data":{"timestamp":" 947158679159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINA"," userResponse":" AKINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158679725","data":{"timestamp":" 947158679725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158680403","data":{"timestamp":" 947158680402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158681011","data":{"timestamp":" 947158681010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158681230","data":{"timestamp":" 947158681229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158681835","data":{"timestamp":" 947158681834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158682346","data":{"timestamp":" 947158682345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huzuni wake ulimzidi haswa alipowaona akina mama tumbili wengine na watoto wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158686313","data":{"timestamp":" 947158686313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158688024","data":{"timestamp":" 947158688023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158689336","data":{"timestamp":" 947158689335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158690866","data":{"timestamp":" 947158690865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158692517","data":{"timestamp":" 947158692517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158693498","data":{"timestamp":" 947158693498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158696085","data":{"timestamp":" 947158696085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158698321","data":{"timestamp":" 947158698320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158698470","data":{"timestamp":" 947158698470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158698473","data":{"timestamp":" 947158698473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158699107","data":{"timestamp":" 947158699107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158700847","data":{"timestamp":" 947158700846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158702798","data":{"timestamp":" 947158702797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158703317","data":{"timestamp":" 947158703317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158704109","data":{"timestamp":" 947158704108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158705780","data":{"timestamp":" 947158705780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158706440","data":{"timestamp":" 947158706439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158706656","data":{"timestamp":" 947158706655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158706881","data":{"timestamp":" 947158706881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili mwenye huzuni alijiwayawaya huku na huku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158710726","data":{"timestamp":" 947158710726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158711742","data":{"timestamp":" 947158711742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158713949","data":{"timestamp":" 947158713948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158715213","data":{"timestamp":" 947158715213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158717408","data":{"timestamp":" 947158717408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158718255","data":{"timestamp":" 947158718255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158718989","data":{"timestamp":" 947158718989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158720498","data":{"timestamp":" 947158720498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158722529","data":{"timestamp":" 947158722528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158724291","data":{"timestamp":" 947158724290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158725800","data":{"timestamp":" 947158725799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158728687","data":{"timestamp":" 947158728687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158729164","data":{"timestamp":" 947158729163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158729782","data":{"timestamp":" 947158729782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158730490","data":{"timestamp":" 947158730489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158730784","data":{"timestamp":" 947158730783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158731318","data":{"timestamp":" 947158731317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijiwayawaya kwenye tawi hili na lile!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158733836","data":{"timestamp":" 947158733836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158735262","data":{"timestamp":" 947158735261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158736663","data":{"timestamp":" 947158736662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158738932","data":{"timestamp":" 947158738932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158739889","data":{"timestamp":" 947158739888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158741719","data":{"timestamp":" 947158741719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158743178","data":{"timestamp":" 947158743177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158744395","data":{"timestamp":" 947158744394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158746660","data":{"timestamp":" 947158746659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158748125","data":{"timestamp":" 947158748125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158750165","data":{"timestamp":" 947158750164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158751897","data":{"timestamp":" 947158751896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158753920","data":{"timestamp":" 947158753919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158755398","data":{"timestamp":" 947158755397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" ZILIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158755775","data":{"timestamp":" 947158755773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158756543","data":{"timestamp":" 947158756542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158757401","data":{"timestamp":" 947158757400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158758261","data":{"timestamp":" 947158758260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158759066","data":{"timestamp":" 947158759065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na tumbili alizidi kulia zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158762681","data":{"timestamp":" 947158762680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158763196","data":{"timestamp":" 947158763195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" START_ALIZAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158769612","data":{"timestamp":" 947158769612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158770386","data":{"timestamp":" 947158770386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158772395","data":{"timestamp":" 947158772394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158773872","data":{"timestamp":" 947158773871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAA"," userResponse":" ALIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158774448","data":{"timestamp":" 947158774448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu alizaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158776850","data":{"timestamp":" 947158776850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158778028","data":{"timestamp":" 947158778028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158779700","data":{"timestamp":" 947158779700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158780285","data":{"timestamp":" 947158780285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158781413","data":{"timestamp":" 947158781413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158783429","data":{"timestamp":" 947158783429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158784508","data":{"timestamp":" 947158784508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158786134","data":{"timestamp":" 947158786133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158787293","data":{"timestamp":" 947158787293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158788581","data":{"timestamp":" 947158788581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158788931","data":{"timestamp":" 947158788931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158790831","data":{"timestamp":" 947158790831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" START_WAMWONE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158791813","data":{"timestamp":" 947158791813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158792908","data":{"timestamp":" 947158792908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158793658","data":{"timestamp":" 947158793658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158794119","data":{"timestamp":" 947158794118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158796412","data":{"timestamp":" 947158796411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158797399","data":{"timestamp":" 947158797398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158798026","data":{"timestamp":" 947158798025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158798511","data":{"timestamp":" 947158798510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158799418","data":{"timestamp":" 947158799417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158800312","data":{"timestamp":" 947158800312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158800942","data":{"timestamp":" 947158800941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPITA"," userResponse":" WAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158801420","data":{"timestamp":" 947158801420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158802542","data":{"timestamp":" 947158802541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMWONE"," userResponse":" WAMWONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158802990","data":{"timestamp":" 947158802989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158804012","data":{"timestamp":" 947158804011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158804622","data":{"timestamp":" 947158804621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliamua kumpeleka mtoto wake njiani ili wapita njia wamwone na kumtakia heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158810228","data":{"timestamp":" 947158810227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158812916","data":{"timestamp":" 947158812916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158813921","data":{"timestamp":" 947158813921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158814666","data":{"timestamp":" 947158814666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158816687","data":{"timestamp":" 947158816686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158817973","data":{"timestamp":" 947158817973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158819184","data":{"timestamp":" 947158819183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" START_NJIANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158820875","data":{"timestamp":" 947158820874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158822899","data":{"timestamp":" 947158822898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158823808","data":{"timestamp":" 947158823807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" ALISHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158824073","data":{"timestamp":" 947158824073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158824943","data":{"timestamp":" 947158824942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158825588","data":{"timestamp":" 947158825587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTOWE"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158826544","data":{"timestamp":" 947158826543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumbili alishuka na kumweka mtotowe njiani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158830222","data":{"timestamp":" 947158830221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158833504","data":{"timestamp":" 947158833504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158833809","data":{"timestamp":" 947158833809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158837013","data":{"timestamp":" 947158837012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158837360","data":{"timestamp":" 947158837359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158838330","data":{"timestamp":" 947158838330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158840055","data":{"timestamp":" 947158840054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158840834","data":{"timestamp":" 947158840834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" MTOTOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158843048","data":{"timestamp":" 947158843048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158844726","data":{"timestamp":" 947158844725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158846142","data":{"timestamp":" 947158846141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158847960","data":{"timestamp":" 947158847959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158848511","data":{"timestamp":" 947158848511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158849695","data":{"timestamp":" 947158849694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158850584","data":{"timestamp":" 947158850583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158851664","data":{"timestamp":" 947158851663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIREJEA"," userResponse":" AKIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158852556","data":{"timestamp":" 947158852555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo mwindaji alikuwa akirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158855327","data":{"timestamp":" 947158855327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMWONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158860122","data":{"timestamp":" 947158860122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158861351","data":{"timestamp":" 947158861351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158862674","data":{"timestamp":" 947158862674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158863048","data":{"timestamp":" 947158863048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158865444","data":{"timestamp":" 947158865443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158865936","data":{"timestamp":" 947158865936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158866542","data":{"timestamp":" 947158866541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158866946","data":{"timestamp":" 947158866946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158869318","data":{"timestamp":" 947158869317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158870007","data":{"timestamp":" 947158870007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158870212","data":{"timestamp":" 947158870211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158871068","data":{"timestamp":" 947158871068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158871898","data":{"timestamp":" 947158871897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALA"," userResponse":" AKILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158872467","data":{"timestamp":" 947158872467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158872668","data":{"timestamp":" 947158872667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158873196","data":{"timestamp":" 947158873195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwona mtoto wa tumbili akilala kando ya njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158877589","data":{"timestamp":" 947158877589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158878397","data":{"timestamp":" 947158878396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158879871","data":{"timestamp":" 947158879871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158881968","data":{"timestamp":" 947158881967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158883559","data":{"timestamp":" 947158883558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158884139","data":{"timestamp":" 947158884139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158885136","data":{"timestamp":" 947158885136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" START_ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158885856","data":{"timestamp":" 947158885856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158888055","data":{"timestamp":" 947158888055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158889071","data":{"timestamp":" 947158889070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158891288","data":{"timestamp":" 947158891287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158892594","data":{"timestamp":" 947158892593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158893541","data":{"timestamp":" 947158893541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158894319","data":{"timestamp":" 947158894318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158894952","data":{"timestamp":" 947158894952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158895517","data":{"timestamp":" 947158895517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158896087","data":{"timestamp":" 947158896086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwindaji alimbeba mwana tumbili hadi nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158899516","data":{"timestamp":" 947158899516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158901394","data":{"timestamp":" 947158901393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158904092","data":{"timestamp":" 947158904092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158905803","data":{"timestamp":" 947158905803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158906912","data":{"timestamp":" 947158906912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" START_WATATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158908547","data":{"timestamp":" 947158908547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158910428","data":{"timestamp":" 947158910428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158912070","data":{"timestamp":" 947158912070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158913892","data":{"timestamp":" 947158913891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158914715","data":{"timestamp":" 947158914715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158916225","data":{"timestamp":" 947158916225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158916393","data":{"timestamp":" 947158916392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158918601","data":{"timestamp":" 947158918601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158919700","data":{"timestamp":" 947158919700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158920783","data":{"timestamp":" 947158920783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158921230","data":{"timestamp":" 947158921229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158921880","data":{"timestamp":" 947158921879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158923241","data":{"timestamp":" 947158923241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158924101","data":{"timestamp":" 947158924100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158924649","data":{"timestamp":" 947158924648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158925411","data":{"timestamp":" 947158925410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani wavulana wake watatu walifurahi kumwona mwana tumbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158930311","data":{"timestamp":" 947158930311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158932685","data":{"timestamp":" 947158932685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" START_WATATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158934194","data":{"timestamp":" 947158934193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158935275","data":{"timestamp":" 947158935274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158937305","data":{"timestamp":" 947158937304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158938445","data":{"timestamp":" 947158938445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158939248","data":{"timestamp":" 947158939248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158940666","data":{"timestamp":" 947158940666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158941589","data":{"timestamp":" 947158941589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158943360","data":{"timestamp":" 947158943359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158943826","data":{"timestamp":" 947158943826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158944987","data":{"timestamp":" 947158944986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158946048","data":{"timestamp":" 947158946047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158946998","data":{"timestamp":" 947158946997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watatu hao waliimba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158949700","data":{"timestamp":" 947158949699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158950212","data":{"timestamp":" 947158950211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158952030","data":{"timestamp":" 947158952030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158953200","data":{"timestamp":" 947158953200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe chini!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158956011","data":{"timestamp":" 947158956011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158956807","data":{"timestamp":" 947158956807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158958606","data":{"timestamp":" 947158958606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158959335","data":{"timestamp":" 947158959334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158962077","data":{"timestamp":" 947158962077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158963481","data":{"timestamp":" 947158963480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158964105","data":{"timestamp":" 947158964105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158965821","data":{"timestamp":" 947158965821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRUSHE"," userResponse":" MRUSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158966890","data":{"timestamp":" 947158966889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mrushe kwake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158968422","data":{"timestamp":" 947158968421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158970080","data":{"timestamp":" 947158970079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158971871","data":{"timestamp":" 947158971871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158974263","data":{"timestamp":" 947158974263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158974764","data":{"timestamp":" 947158974763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158976578","data":{"timestamp":" 947158976578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158978472","data":{"timestamp":" 947158978472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158979758","data":{"timestamp":" 947158979758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158981082","data":{"timestamp":" 947158981082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" START_MWINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158982771","data":{"timestamp":" 947158982771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158984504","data":{"timestamp":" 947158984503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158985503","data":{"timestamp":" 947158985503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158986742","data":{"timestamp":" 947158986741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIRUSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158988000","data":{"timestamp":" 947158987999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158988408","data":{"timestamp":" 947158988407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158989280","data":{"timestamp":" 947158989279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158989912","data":{"timestamp":" 947158989912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158990734","data":{"timestamp":" 947158990733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwana tumbili alirushwa kutoka kwa mmoja hadi mwingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158996613","data":{"timestamp":" 947158996613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947158998495","data":{"timestamp":" 947158998494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" START_WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159000178","data":{"timestamp":" 947159000178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159001943","data":{"timestamp":" 947159001942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159002030","data":{"timestamp":" 947159002029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159004570","data":{"timestamp":" 947159004569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159006604","data":{"timestamp":" 947159006603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159008480","data":{"timestamp":" 947159008480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" START_TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159009932","data":{"timestamp":" 947159009932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159010655","data":{"timestamp":" 947159010655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159011364","data":{"timestamp":" 947159011364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159012491","data":{"timestamp":" 947159012491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159013444","data":{"timestamp":" 947159013443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159016708","data":{"timestamp":" 947159016708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159018364","data":{"timestamp":" 947159018363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159019631","data":{"timestamp":" 947159019631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159021876","data":{"timestamp":" 947159021876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159022174","data":{"timestamp":" 947159022173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159024086","data":{"timestamp":" 947159024086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159025866","data":{"timestamp":" 947159025866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159027147","data":{"timestamp":" 947159027147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159028870","data":{"timestamp":" 947159028870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" START_MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159030130","data":{"timestamp":" 947159030130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159031798","data":{"timestamp":" 947159031797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159032582","data":{"timestamp":" 947159032582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159033811","data":{"timestamp":" 947159033810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159034376","data":{"timestamp":" 947159034375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159034603","data":{"timestamp":" 947159034602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159035364","data":{"timestamp":" 947159035363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159035579","data":{"timestamp":" 947159035579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159035873","data":{"timestamp":" 947159035872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159036004","data":{"timestamp":" 947159036003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159036766","data":{"timestamp":" 947159036766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159037190","data":{"timestamp":" 947159037189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159037905","data":{"timestamp":" 947159037905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159037943","data":{"timestamp":" 947159037943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159038115","data":{"timestamp":" 947159038114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wale walipoendelea kucheza na mwana tumbili tumbili alijificha mtini na kuangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159045134","data":{"timestamp":" 947159045134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159046980","data":{"timestamp":" 947159046980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159047377","data":{"timestamp":" 947159047377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159049050","data":{"timestamp":" 947159049050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159050515","data":{"timestamp":" 947159050515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159050811","data":{"timestamp":" 947159050811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159052140","data":{"timestamp":" 947159052140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159054026","data":{"timestamp":" 947159054026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159055886","data":{"timestamp":" 947159055886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159056970","data":{"timestamp":" 947159056969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159058331","data":{"timestamp":" 947159058331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159059563","data":{"timestamp":" 947159059563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159060098","data":{"timestamp":" 947159060098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" START_WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159062053","data":{"timestamp":" 947159062052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159064448","data":{"timestamp":" 947159064447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159065020","data":{"timestamp":" 947159065019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159065807","data":{"timestamp":" 947159065807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159066362","data":{"timestamp":" 947159066361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159067541","data":{"timestamp":" 947159067540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159068508","data":{"timestamp":" 947159068507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEFARIKI"," userResponse":" ANGEFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159069006","data":{"timestamp":" 947159069006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159069831","data":{"timestamp":" 947159069830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliogopa kuwa mtoto huyu naye angefariki kama wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159073567","data":{"timestamp":" 947159073566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159073579","data":{"timestamp":" 947159073579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159077758","data":{"timestamp":" 947159077758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159078306","data":{"timestamp":" 947159078306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" START_MWINDAJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159079773","data":{"timestamp":" 947159079773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159081222","data":{"timestamp":" 947159081221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159082839","data":{"timestamp":" 947159082839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159084507","data":{"timestamp":" 947159084506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159085084","data":{"timestamp":" 947159085083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159088785","data":{"timestamp":" 947159088785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159090725","data":{"timestamp":" 947159090724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" START_WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159092578","data":{"timestamp":" 947159092577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159094029","data":{"timestamp":" 947159094029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159095258","data":{"timestamp":" 947159095258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159096293","data":{"timestamp":" 947159096292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159098097","data":{"timestamp":" 947159098096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159098749","data":{"timestamp":" 947159098748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159098965","data":{"timestamp":" 947159098964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159099993","data":{"timestamp":" 947159099992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" MWINDAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159101022","data":{"timestamp":" 947159101022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159101843","data":{"timestamp":" 947159101842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159103030","data":{"timestamp":" 947159103030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159103368","data":{"timestamp":" 947159103367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159104359","data":{"timestamp":" 947159104358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159105005","data":{"timestamp":" 947159105004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara mke wa mwindaji aliwaona watoto wakicheza na tumbili mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159110937","data":{"timestamp":" 947159110936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159113009","data":{"timestamp":" 947159113009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159114876","data":{"timestamp":" 947159114876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159116236","data":{"timestamp":" 947159116236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159119882","data":{"timestamp":" 947159119882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159121844","data":{"timestamp":" 947159121843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159123697","data":{"timestamp":" 947159123696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159126097","data":{"timestamp":" 947159126096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONYA"," userResponse":" ALIWAONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159127394","data":{"timestamp":" 947159127394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159128471","data":{"timestamp":" 947159128471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAANGALIFU"," userResponse":" WAANGALIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159131213","data":{"timestamp":" 947159131212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159132884","data":{"timestamp":" 947159132884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159133226","data":{"timestamp":" 947159133226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159134869","data":{"timestamp":" 947159134868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159135396","data":{"timestamp":" 947159135395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLETE"," userResponse":" MLETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159135990","data":{"timestamp":" 947159135989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu mlete hapa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159140821","data":{"timestamp":" 947159140820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159142036","data":{"timestamp":" 947159142035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159143916","data":{"timestamp":" 947159143916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159144806","data":{"timestamp":" 947159144804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159145895","data":{"timestamp":" 947159145894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159149194","data":{"timestamp":" 947159149194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159151576","data":{"timestamp":" 947159151576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159152893","data":{"timestamp":" 947159152892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159156226","data":{"timestamp":" 947159156225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159158698","data":{"timestamp":" 947159158698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159160558","data":{"timestamp":" 947159160557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159161709","data":{"timestamp":" 947159161709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159162916","data":{"timestamp":" 947159162915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159163349","data":{"timestamp":" 947159163348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159164047","data":{"timestamp":" 947159164046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159164062","data":{"timestamp":" 947159164061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONONI"," userResponse":" MIKONONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159164682","data":{"timestamp":" 947159164681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159164873","data":{"timestamp":" 947159164873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159165248","data":{"timestamp":" 947159165248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimchukuwa mwana tumbili mikononi mwake na kumbariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMBARIKI"," userResponse":" KUMBARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159174942","data":{"timestamp":" 947159174942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159179716","data":{"timestamp":" 947159179716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159181618","data":{"timestamp":" 947159181617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159183294","data":{"timestamp":" 947159183293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159185112","data":{"timestamp":" 947159185112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159186610","data":{"timestamp":" 947159186609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159189000","data":{"timestamp":" 947159188999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159190001","data":{"timestamp":" 947159190000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159190861","data":{"timestamp":" 947159190860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159192492","data":{"timestamp":" 947159192492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159195250","data":{"timestamp":" 947159195249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159196194","data":{"timestamp":" 947159196193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159198082","data":{"timestamp":" 947159198082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159199458","data":{"timestamp":" 947159199458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159199562","data":{"timestamp":" 947159199562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159201933","data":{"timestamp":" 947159201933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159202407","data":{"timestamp":" 947159202406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159203125","data":{"timestamp":" 947159203124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159203862","data":{"timestamp":" 947159203861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159204909","data":{"timestamp":" 947159204909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBILI"," userResponse":" TUMBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159205953","data":{"timestamp":" 947159205952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159206300","data":{"timestamp":" 947159206299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159207102","data":{"timestamp":" 947159207100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipomweka mwana tumbili chini tumbili alikimbia kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159217001","data":{"timestamp":" 947159217001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159218492","data":{"timestamp":" 947159218492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159220379","data":{"timestamp":" 947159220379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159221359","data":{"timestamp":" 947159221359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159223232","data":{"timestamp":" 947159223231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159224894","data":{"timestamp":" 947159224894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159226513","data":{"timestamp":" 947159226513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159227404","data":{"timestamp":" 947159227404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159229341","data":{"timestamp":" 947159229341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159231678","data":{"timestamp":" 947159231677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMBEBA"," userResponse":" ALIMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159232544","data":{"timestamp":" 947159232544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159233743","data":{"timestamp":" 947159233742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUANI"," userResponse":" KIFUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159233965","data":{"timestamp":" 947159233964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159234742","data":{"timestamp":" 947159234742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159235629","data":{"timestamp":" 947159235629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159238414","data":{"timestamp":" 947159238410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159238538","data":{"timestamp":" 947159238538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9483b749-e529-4e4e-9c2a-a535b2da6789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimbeba mwanawe kifuani na kwenda mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159254058","data":{"timestamp":" 947159254057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" runinga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159259177","data":{"timestamp":" 947159259177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" runinga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159260767","data":{"timestamp":" 947159260766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfereji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159264283","data":{"timestamp":" 947159264283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfereji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" START_MFEREJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159265506","data":{"timestamp":" 947159265506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfereji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159267107","data":{"timestamp":" 947159267107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuongea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159270000","data":{"timestamp":" 947159270000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuongea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159271601","data":{"timestamp":" 947159271601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159274800","data":{"timestamp":" 947159274800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159276426","data":{"timestamp":" 947159276425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159279492","data":{"timestamp":" 947159279491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159281087","data":{"timestamp":" 947159281086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" unanuka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNANUKA"," userResponse":" UNANUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159284233","data":{"timestamp":" 947159284233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" unanuka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNANUKA"," userResponse":" UNANUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159285831","data":{"timestamp":" 947159285830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ninaona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAONA"," userResponse":" NINAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159288954","data":{"timestamp":" 947159288954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ninaona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAONA"," userResponse":" NINAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159290558","data":{"timestamp":" 947159290558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" unataka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATAKA"," userResponse":" UNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159293235","data":{"timestamp":" 947159293234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" unataka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATAKA"," userResponse":" UNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159294830","data":{"timestamp":" 947159294829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kifalme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159297449","data":{"timestamp":" 947159297448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kifalme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" KIFALME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159299053","data":{"timestamp":" 947159299052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159301818","data":{"timestamp":" 947159301818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159303839","data":{"timestamp":" 947159303838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159303954","data":{"timestamp":" 947159303954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e4ff21b9-1ce5-4824-9838-57be111aa6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159320499","data":{"timestamp":" 947159320498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159321045","data":{"timestamp":" 947159321044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159322152","data":{"timestamp":" 947159322151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159323351","data":{"timestamp":" 947159323351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159323636","data":{"timestamp":" 947159323635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159324315","data":{"timestamp":" 947159324314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159324733","data":{"timestamp":" 947159324733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159325433","data":{"timestamp":" 947159325432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" PEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159326803","data":{"timestamp":" 947159326802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIAMUA"," userResponse":" KILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159327242","data":{"timestamp":" 947159327242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159327483","data":{"timestamp":" 947159327483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159327580","data":{"timestamp":" 947159327580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159336319","data":{"timestamp":" 947159336319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 6d148d9d-1ee3-4fb6-83bc-c9cfa43296f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita kikundi cha wanyama wenye pembe kiliamua kuwa na sherehe kubwa milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159350867","data":{"timestamp":" 947159350867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_anaitwa_ambacho-anaitwa-mwilini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" anaitwa"," userResponse":" anaitwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159356077","data":{"timestamp":" 947159356077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kayanja_kayanja-maswali-kikubwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kayanja"," userResponse":" kayanja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159363475","data":{"timestamp":" 947159363474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nilijua_nilijua-alipata-magunia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nilijua"," userResponse":" nilijua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159368309","data":{"timestamp":" 947159368309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akasema_akasema-ninajua-matunda"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akasema"," userResponse":" akasema"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159373679","data":{"timestamp":" 947159373679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_gingile_akadeli-gingile-kuogopa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gingile"," userResponse":" gingile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159380448","data":{"timestamp":" 947159380448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unywele_magozwe-haikuwa-unywele"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unywele"," userResponse":" unywele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159386416","data":{"timestamp":" 947159386416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_wenyewe-alifika-refiloe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" wenyewe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159392979","data":{"timestamp":" 947159392979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_wenyewe-alifika-refiloe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159398521","data":{"timestamp":" 947159398521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mandazi_mandazi-michafu-kumpiga"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mandazi"," userResponse":" mandazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159403952","data":{"timestamp":" 947159403952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akaruka_akaruka-anasema-kitoweo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akaruka"," userResponse":" akaruka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159412776","data":{"timestamp":" 947159412776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuliita_kuliita-kawaida-akapata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuliita"," userResponse":" kuliita"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159418569","data":{"timestamp":" 947159418568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 59dee2a2-1bcb-4688-9506-46692cba6c67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kuliita_kuliita-kawaida-akapata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159432852","data":{"timestamp":" 947159432852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159437377","data":{"timestamp":" 947159437377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159446477","data":{"timestamp":" 947159446477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159453633","data":{"timestamp":" 947159453633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159460227","data":{"timestamp":" 947159460227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159466610","data":{"timestamp":" 947159466610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159474294","data":{"timestamp":" 947159474294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" kitenge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159481648","data":{"timestamp":" 947159481648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" akiimba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159487978","data":{"timestamp":" 947159487978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159501417","data":{"timestamp":" 947159501417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" angempa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159510611","data":{"timestamp":" 947159510611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" kibichi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159517777","data":{"timestamp":" 947159517777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159522874","data":{"timestamp":" 947159522873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" dhahabu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159528838","data":{"timestamp":" 947159528837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159535074","data":{"timestamp":" 947159535073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" hadithi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159543109","data":{"timestamp":" 947159543109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159548902","data":{"timestamp":" 947159548901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" a554fa63-aa47-4bb3-b286-a5cbd5c9f59d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159561227","data":{"timestamp":" 947159561227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" dhahabu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159567603","data":{"timestamp":" 947159567603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159591820","data":{"timestamp":" 947159591820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159598589","data":{"timestamp":" 947159598589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159604062","data":{"timestamp":" 947159604062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" akaruka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159610900","data":{"timestamp":" 947159610899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159616100","data":{"timestamp":" 947159616100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159622391","data":{"timestamp":" 947159622391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159627935","data":{"timestamp":" 947159627935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" kibichi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159634259","data":{"timestamp":" 947159634259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" angempa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159640490","data":{"timestamp":" 947159640490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159645368","data":{"timestamp":" 947159645368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" utapata"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159651224","data":{"timestamp":" 947159651224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" anataka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159657354","data":{"timestamp":" 947159657354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159662844","data":{"timestamp":" 947159662844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" akaruka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159670288","data":{"timestamp":" 947159670287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159676528","data":{"timestamp":" 947159676528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" kitenge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159682590","data":{"timestamp":" 947159682590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159688347","data":{"timestamp":" 947159688345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" c4210cde-16a6-4943-b465-f039c87744a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159709426","data":{"timestamp":" 947159709426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159714831","data":{"timestamp":" 947159714831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159719663","data":{"timestamp":" 947159719662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159726404","data":{"timestamp":" 947159726403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159731646","data":{"timestamp":" 947159731645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159736844","data":{"timestamp":" 947159736844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" kitenge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159743075","data":{"timestamp":" 947159743075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159748994","data":{"timestamp":" 947159748994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" akaruka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159755205","data":{"timestamp":" 947159755205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" nyamani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159761427","data":{"timestamp":" 947159761426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159766915","data":{"timestamp":" 947159766915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" nitumie"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159773454","data":{"timestamp":" 947159773454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159778628","data":{"timestamp":" 947159778628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159785898","data":{"timestamp":" 947159785898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" kibichi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159794269","data":{"timestamp":" 947159794269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159800055","data":{"timestamp":" 947159800054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3f7550e7-e56a-4191-9f7d-7d5960585bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159813419","data":{"timestamp":" 947159813418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" nitumie"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159819785","data":{"timestamp":" 947159819785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159824798","data":{"timestamp":" 947159824798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159836360","data":{"timestamp":" 947159836360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" hadithi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159842634","data":{"timestamp":" 947159842634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" alisema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159849557","data":{"timestamp":" 947159849556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159860468","data":{"timestamp":" 947159860468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159868661","data":{"timestamp":" 947159868661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159877322","data":{"timestamp":" 947159877322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159887442","data":{"timestamp":" 947159887442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159892556","data":{"timestamp":" 947159892556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159899375","data":{"timestamp":" 947159899375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kusikia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159905088","data":{"timestamp":" 947159905088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159914337","data":{"timestamp":" 947159914337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159920139","data":{"timestamp":" 947159920137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 120ec97d-0526-498b-ac0f-458f3d5e32e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159944611","data":{"timestamp":" 947159944611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159949870","data":{"timestamp":" 947159949870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159954881","data":{"timestamp":" 947159954881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159966740","data":{"timestamp":" 947159966740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159977440","data":{"timestamp":" 947159977439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159985392","data":{"timestamp":" 947159985392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159991648","data":{"timestamp":" 947159991648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" aliamka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947159997923","data":{"timestamp":" 947159997922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alipiga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160004171","data":{"timestamp":" 947160004171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160010436","data":{"timestamp":" 947160010435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160019515","data":{"timestamp":" 947160019515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160031688","data":{"timestamp":" 947160031688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" kitenge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160037962","data":{"timestamp":" 947160037962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" akiimba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160044348","data":{"timestamp":" 947160044348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160050116","data":{"timestamp":" 947160050114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e348bdfd-5c09-4159-af70-3a3a9ecb6ca5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160064113","data":{"timestamp":" 947160064113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliweza_nitumie-aliweza-akaruka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliweza"," userResponse":" aliweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160069671","data":{"timestamp":" 947160069671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kikombe_kikombe-akaruka-nyamani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kikombe"," userResponse":" kikombe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160075067","data":{"timestamp":" 947160075066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuvutia_dhahabu-kuvutia-kusikia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuvutia"," userResponse":" kuvutia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160083107","data":{"timestamp":" 947160083107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_muthoni_muthoni-alisema-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muthoni"," userResponse":" muthoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160090440","data":{"timestamp":" 947160090440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutumia_kutumia-utapata-anataka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutumia"," userResponse":" kutumia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160095657","data":{"timestamp":" 947160095657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ataweza_ataweza-hakujua-kuvutia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ataweza"," userResponse":" ataweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160101904","data":{"timestamp":" 947160101903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_alifika-alipiga-aliamka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160108231","data":{"timestamp":" 947160108230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwavuli_kitenge-akiimba-mwavuli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwavuli"," userResponse":" mwavuli"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160116901","data":{"timestamp":" 947160116900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninajua_ninajua-kuchoma-kimejaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninajua"," userResponse":" ninajua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160124975","data":{"timestamp":" 947160124975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unaweza"," userResponse":" unaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160130752","data":{"timestamp":" 947160130751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" e46d9a8b-ee78-41f7-928f-d87fc3d6f03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.noShow.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_unaweza_kibichi-unaweza-angempa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160144414","data":{"timestamp":" 947160144414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160144967","data":{"timestamp":" 947160144967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160145969","data":{"timestamp":" 947160145968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160146560","data":{"timestamp":" 947160146560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160147274","data":{"timestamp":" 947160147274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160151230","data":{"timestamp":" 947160151230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160151332","data":{"timestamp":" 947160151332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160163915","data":{"timestamp":" 947160163915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 360197ce-971e-4fa0-a4f9-2fd4eb1342aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160188731","data":{"timestamp":" 947160188731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160195394","data":{"timestamp":" 947160195394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160202058","data":{"timestamp":" 947160202058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160209508","data":{"timestamp":" 947160209507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160220293","data":{"timestamp":" 947160220293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160226940","data":{"timestamp":" 947160226939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160233585","data":{"timestamp":" 947160233585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160240195","data":{"timestamp":" 947160240195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160246808","data":{"timestamp":" 947160246807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160254313","data":{"timestamp":" 947160254313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160260931","data":{"timestamp":" 947160260931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160268443","data":{"timestamp":" 947160268443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160275098","data":{"timestamp":" 947160275098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160281706","data":{"timestamp":" 947160281705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160289202","data":{"timestamp":" 947160289202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160301294","data":{"timestamp":" 947160301294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 01486d6c-4c4b-4889-a692-a0a43ed90e75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160324717","data":{"timestamp":" 947160324716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160331371","data":{"timestamp":" 947160331370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160338017","data":{"timestamp":" 947160338017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160344694","data":{"timestamp":" 947160344694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160351353","data":{"timestamp":" 947160351352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160357991","data":{"timestamp":" 947160357991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160364620","data":{"timestamp":" 947160364620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160372080","data":{"timestamp":" 947160372080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160382954","data":{"timestamp":" 947160382953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160389577","data":{"timestamp":" 947160389577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160396201","data":{"timestamp":" 947160396201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160403665","data":{"timestamp":" 947160403665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160411531","data":{"timestamp":" 947160411531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 22ece16f-f2dc-4da8-966d-6d663c943789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160434851","data":{"timestamp":" 947160434849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160441509","data":{"timestamp":" 947160441508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160448176","data":{"timestamp":" 947160448176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160454865","data":{"timestamp":" 947160454864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160462322","data":{"timestamp":" 947160462322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160468953","data":{"timestamp":" 947160468953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160476441","data":{"timestamp":" 947160476440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160487129","data":{"timestamp":" 947160487129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160493310","data":{"timestamp":" 947160493310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160500761","data":{"timestamp":" 947160500760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160507380","data":{"timestamp":" 947160507380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sikujua_mvulana_akaosha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160513979","data":{"timestamp":" 947160513978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160521443","data":{"timestamp":" 947160521443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160531912","data":{"timestamp":" 947160531911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuzirai_waliuza_kuchuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160538550","data":{"timestamp":" 947160538550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maathai_wasiiue_aliamru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160545193","data":{"timestamp":" 947160545192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160552669","data":{"timestamp":" 947160552669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160563505","data":{"timestamp":" 947160563505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160570915","data":{"timestamp":" 947160570914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160588713","data":{"timestamp":" 947160588713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9f707d7c-c87a-4bb1-af08-e967f08c28cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_jingine_mwepesi_ulienea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160613226","data":{"timestamp":" 947160613225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" ae6490ca-5ec7-4cd1-925a-9e8a15af6bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160619881","data":{"timestamp":" 947160619880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" ae6490ca-5ec7-4cd1-925a-9e8a15af6bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160626546","data":{"timestamp":" 947160626546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" ae6490ca-5ec7-4cd1-925a-9e8a15af6bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160630349","data":{"timestamp":" 947160630349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" ae6490ca-5ec7-4cd1-925a-9e8a15af6bc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160654195","data":{"timestamp":" 947160654195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alihepa_ghafula_kunukia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160660838","data":{"timestamp":" 947160660837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akitaka_amewaua_mekundu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160667465","data":{"timestamp":" 947160667464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumbuka_kakangu_vikubwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160674087","data":{"timestamp":" 947160674087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160681545","data":{"timestamp":" 947160681545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amshike_mwangza_aliitoa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160688172","data":{"timestamp":" 947160688172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160695624","data":{"timestamp":" 947160695622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160706283","data":{"timestamp":" 947160706282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuepuka_urafiki_tulijua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160712947","data":{"timestamp":" 947160712947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160720400","data":{"timestamp":" 947160720400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160731108","data":{"timestamp":" 947160731108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.7.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160733263","data":{"timestamp":" 947160733263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 1eeacfaa-a2a9-4f32-b4f8-573328486cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.7.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_utavuna_kupanga_aliumwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160750529","data":{"timestamp":" 947160750528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160751165","data":{"timestamp":" 947160751164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160751421","data":{"timestamp":" 947160751421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160751990","data":{"timestamp":" 947160751989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160753151","data":{"timestamp":" 947160753150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160753920","data":{"timestamp":" 947160753919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160755342","data":{"timestamp":" 947160755341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160756245","data":{"timestamp":" 947160756244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160756881","data":{"timestamp":" 947160756881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160757825","data":{"timestamp":" 947160757824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160758477","data":{"timestamp":" 947160758476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160760856","data":{"timestamp":" 947160760855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160761107","data":{"timestamp":" 947160761106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160762043","data":{"timestamp":" 947160762043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160762937","data":{"timestamp":" 947160762935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160763792","data":{"timestamp":" 947160763791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160764700","data":{"timestamp":" 947160764700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160767498","data":{"timestamp":" 947160767497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160767930","data":{"timestamp":" 947160767929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160768639","data":{"timestamp":" 947160768638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160769702","data":{"timestamp":" 947160769701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160770639","data":{"timestamp":" 947160770638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160771469","data":{"timestamp":" 947160771468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160772426","data":{"timestamp":" 947160772425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160774041","data":{"timestamp":" 947160774041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160774251","data":{"timestamp":" 947160774250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160775111","data":{"timestamp":" 947160775111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160775828","data":{"timestamp":" 947160775827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160776132","data":{"timestamp":" 947160776132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160777015","data":{"timestamp":" 947160777015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160778093","data":{"timestamp":" 947160778092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160781148","data":{"timestamp":" 947160781147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160781770","data":{"timestamp":" 947160781770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160782882","data":{"timestamp":" 947160782881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160784033","data":{"timestamp":" 947160784033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160784387","data":{"timestamp":" 947160784387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160785268","data":{"timestamp":" 947160785267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160786512","data":{"timestamp":" 947160786512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160787355","data":{"timestamp":" 947160787355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160789960","data":{"timestamp":" 947160789959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160790858","data":{"timestamp":" 947160790858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160791447","data":{"timestamp":" 947160791446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160791700","data":{"timestamp":" 947160791696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160792430","data":{"timestamp":" 947160792429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160793245","data":{"timestamp":" 947160793244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160795911","data":{"timestamp":" 947160795910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160796905","data":{"timestamp":" 947160796904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160797384","data":{"timestamp":" 947160797384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160797655","data":{"timestamp":" 947160797654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160798450","data":{"timestamp":" 947160798449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160799759","data":{"timestamp":" 947160799758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160800099","data":{"timestamp":" 947160800098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160801343","data":{"timestamp":" 947160801341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160802269","data":{"timestamp":" 947160802268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160802935","data":{"timestamp":" 947160802934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160803188","data":{"timestamp":" 947160803187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160804053","data":{"timestamp":" 947160804053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160804596","data":{"timestamp":" 947160804596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160805187","data":{"timestamp":" 947160805187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160805759","data":{"timestamp":" 947160805759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160808500","data":{"timestamp":" 947160808499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160809768","data":{"timestamp":" 947160809767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160810790","data":{"timestamp":" 947160810790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160812148","data":{"timestamp":" 947160812148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160813201","data":{"timestamp":" 947160813201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160813742","data":{"timestamp":" 947160813741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160814902","data":{"timestamp":" 947160814902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160816357","data":{"timestamp":" 947160816356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160817501","data":{"timestamp":" 947160817500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160818048","data":{"timestamp":" 947160818048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160819007","data":{"timestamp":" 947160819007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160821516","data":{"timestamp":" 947160821516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160822497","data":{"timestamp":" 947160822496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160822811","data":{"timestamp":" 947160822811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160823585","data":{"timestamp":" 947160823585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160824956","data":{"timestamp":" 947160824956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160825616","data":{"timestamp":" 947160825616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160826031","data":{"timestamp":" 947160826030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160826866","data":{"timestamp":" 947160826866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160827892","data":{"timestamp":" 947160827892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160828358","data":{"timestamp":" 947160828358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160829294","data":{"timestamp":" 947160829294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160829479","data":{"timestamp":" 947160829479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160830243","data":{"timestamp":" 947160830243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160832988","data":{"timestamp":" 947160832988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160833983","data":{"timestamp":" 947160833983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160834938","data":{"timestamp":" 947160834938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160836152","data":{"timestamp":" 947160836152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160836794","data":{"timestamp":" 947160836794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160837950","data":{"timestamp":" 947160837949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160838778","data":{"timestamp":" 947160838778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160839534","data":{"timestamp":" 947160839533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160839704","data":{"timestamp":" 947160839704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160840471","data":{"timestamp":" 947160840471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160843699","data":{"timestamp":" 947160843698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160844991","data":{"timestamp":" 947160844991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160845840","data":{"timestamp":" 947160845840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160848025","data":{"timestamp":" 947160848025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160848911","data":{"timestamp":" 947160848910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160850151","data":{"timestamp":" 947160850150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160850842","data":{"timestamp":" 947160850842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160851413","data":{"timestamp":" 947160851413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160852039","data":{"timestamp":" 947160852039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160853054","data":{"timestamp":" 947160853054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160853439","data":{"timestamp":" 947160853439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160854154","data":{"timestamp":" 947160854154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160854642","data":{"timestamp":" 947160854641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160855087","data":{"timestamp":" 947160855086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160855692","data":{"timestamp":" 947160855692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160858117","data":{"timestamp":" 947160858117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160859790","data":{"timestamp":" 947160859790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160860934","data":{"timestamp":" 947160860934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160861698","data":{"timestamp":" 947160861698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160862163","data":{"timestamp":" 947160862162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160863227","data":{"timestamp":" 947160863226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160863781","data":{"timestamp":" 947160863781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160866432","data":{"timestamp":" 947160866432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160867359","data":{"timestamp":" 947160867358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160868080","data":{"timestamp":" 947160868080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160868264","data":{"timestamp":" 947160868263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160868790","data":{"timestamp":" 947160868790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160869520","data":{"timestamp":" 947160869519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160870087","data":{"timestamp":" 947160870087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160872997","data":{"timestamp":" 947160872997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160873625","data":{"timestamp":" 947160873624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160876928","data":{"timestamp":" 947160876927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160878329","data":{"timestamp":" 947160878329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160878620","data":{"timestamp":" 947160878619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160879492","data":{"timestamp":" 947160879491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160880763","data":{"timestamp":" 947160880762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160881645","data":{"timestamp":" 947160881645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160881746","data":{"timestamp":" 947160881745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160882099","data":{"timestamp":" 947160882098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160883163","data":{"timestamp":" 947160883162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160884117","data":{"timestamp":" 947160884116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160886112","data":{"timestamp":" 947160886112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160886963","data":{"timestamp":" 947160886962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160887068","data":{"timestamp":" 947160887068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160888056","data":{"timestamp":" 947160888056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160889529","data":{"timestamp":" 947160889529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160890595","data":{"timestamp":" 947160890595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160892159","data":{"timestamp":" 947160892159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160892713","data":{"timestamp":" 947160892713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160893465","data":{"timestamp":" 947160893464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160896494","data":{"timestamp":" 947160896493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160897738","data":{"timestamp":" 947160897737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160898532","data":{"timestamp":" 947160898532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160899629","data":{"timestamp":" 947160899628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160900214","data":{"timestamp":" 947160900213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160901197","data":{"timestamp":" 947160901196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160902054","data":{"timestamp":" 947160902053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160903176","data":{"timestamp":" 947160903176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160904276","data":{"timestamp":" 947160904275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160907032","data":{"timestamp":" 947160907031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160908055","data":{"timestamp":" 947160908054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160909759","data":{"timestamp":" 947160909758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160910395","data":{"timestamp":" 947160910395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160910802","data":{"timestamp":" 947160910801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160911642","data":{"timestamp":" 947160911641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160914480","data":{"timestamp":" 947160914480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160915668","data":{"timestamp":" 947160915668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160916273","data":{"timestamp":" 947160916273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160917123","data":{"timestamp":" 947160917123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160918415","data":{"timestamp":" 947160918414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160919292","data":{"timestamp":" 947160919292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160920422","data":{"timestamp":" 947160920422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160920916","data":{"timestamp":" 947160920916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160921517","data":{"timestamp":" 947160921516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160922390","data":{"timestamp":" 947160922389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160923042","data":{"timestamp":" 947160923042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160923706","data":{"timestamp":" 947160923706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160924231","data":{"timestamp":" 947160924231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160924985","data":{"timestamp":" 947160924985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160925469","data":{"timestamp":" 947160925468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160926006","data":{"timestamp":" 947160926005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160926997","data":{"timestamp":" 947160926997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160927269","data":{"timestamp":" 947160927269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160928158","data":{"timestamp":" 947160928158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160930240","data":{"timestamp":" 947160930239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160931107","data":{"timestamp":" 947160931106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160932052","data":{"timestamp":" 947160932051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160932683","data":{"timestamp":" 947160932682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160932914","data":{"timestamp":" 947160932914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160933859","data":{"timestamp":" 947160933858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160935009","data":{"timestamp":" 947160935008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160935562","data":{"timestamp":" 947160935562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160936365","data":{"timestamp":" 947160936365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160937162","data":{"timestamp":" 947160937162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160937759","data":{"timestamp":" 947160937758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160938612","data":{"timestamp":" 947160938611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160939497","data":{"timestamp":" 947160939496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160940350","data":{"timestamp":" 947160940349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160941065","data":{"timestamp":" 947160941065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160943047","data":{"timestamp":" 947160943046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160943604","data":{"timestamp":" 947160943603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160944596","data":{"timestamp":" 947160944595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160945280","data":{"timestamp":" 947160945280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160948616","data":{"timestamp":" 947160948616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160949997","data":{"timestamp":" 947160949996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160950241","data":{"timestamp":" 947160950240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160950641","data":{"timestamp":" 947160950640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160951491","data":{"timestamp":" 947160951491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160952824","data":{"timestamp":" 947160952823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160954448","data":{"timestamp":" 947160954447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160954700","data":{"timestamp":" 947160954699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160955784","data":{"timestamp":" 947160955784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160957381","data":{"timestamp":" 947160957381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160958897","data":{"timestamp":" 947160958896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160959697","data":{"timestamp":" 947160959697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160959807","data":{"timestamp":" 947160959806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160960478","data":{"timestamp":" 947160960478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160961379","data":{"timestamp":" 947160961378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160963405","data":{"timestamp":" 947160963405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160963654","data":{"timestamp":" 947160963654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160964393","data":{"timestamp":" 947160964392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160965303","data":{"timestamp":" 947160965303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160965531","data":{"timestamp":" 947160965531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160966776","data":{"timestamp":" 947160966776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160969222","data":{"timestamp":" 947160969221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160969635","data":{"timestamp":" 947160969635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160970340","data":{"timestamp":" 947160970339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160971264","data":{"timestamp":" 947160971263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160972299","data":{"timestamp":" 947160972298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160973504","data":{"timestamp":" 947160973503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160974187","data":{"timestamp":" 947160974186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160975391","data":{"timestamp":" 947160975391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160976039","data":{"timestamp":" 947160976038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160976871","data":{"timestamp":" 947160976871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160977028","data":{"timestamp":" 947160977028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160978060","data":{"timestamp":" 947160978059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160980322","data":{"timestamp":" 947160980321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160980841","data":{"timestamp":" 947160980840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160981679","data":{"timestamp":" 947160981679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160984585","data":{"timestamp":" 947160984584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160985298","data":{"timestamp":" 947160985297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160985917","data":{"timestamp":" 947160985916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160986780","data":{"timestamp":" 947160986779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160987824","data":{"timestamp":" 947160987823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160990000","data":{"timestamp":" 947160990000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160990450","data":{"timestamp":" 947160990449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160991442","data":{"timestamp":" 947160991441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160992610","data":{"timestamp":" 947160992608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160993757","data":{"timestamp":" 947160993756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160994549","data":{"timestamp":" 947160994548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160996057","data":{"timestamp":" 947160996056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160996994","data":{"timestamp":" 947160996992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160998327","data":{"timestamp":" 947160998327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160998860","data":{"timestamp":" 947160998859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947160999491","data":{"timestamp":" 947160999491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161000353","data":{"timestamp":" 947161000352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161001190","data":{"timestamp":" 947161001189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161001829","data":{"timestamp":" 947161001828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161002387","data":{"timestamp":" 947161002387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161003144","data":{"timestamp":" 947161003144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161003666","data":{"timestamp":" 947161003665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161004258","data":{"timestamp":" 947161004256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161004469","data":{"timestamp":" 947161004468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161005149","data":{"timestamp":" 947161005149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161005994","data":{"timestamp":" 947161005993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161008500","data":{"timestamp":" 947161008500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161008880","data":{"timestamp":" 947161008877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161009543","data":{"timestamp":" 947161009543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161010336","data":{"timestamp":" 947161010335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161010583","data":{"timestamp":" 947161010582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161011075","data":{"timestamp":" 947161011074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161011896","data":{"timestamp":" 947161011895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161012682","data":{"timestamp":" 947161012682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161013755","data":{"timestamp":" 947161013755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161014359","data":{"timestamp":" 947161014358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161017608","data":{"timestamp":" 947161017607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161018365","data":{"timestamp":" 947161018364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161019362","data":{"timestamp":" 947161019362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161020238","data":{"timestamp":" 947161020237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161021298","data":{"timestamp":" 947161021298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161021798","data":{"timestamp":" 947161021797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161022877","data":{"timestamp":" 947161022877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161024049","data":{"timestamp":" 947161024049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161025412","data":{"timestamp":" 947161025411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161025766","data":{"timestamp":" 947161025766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161026460","data":{"timestamp":" 947161026459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161026759","data":{"timestamp":" 947161026759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161027802","data":{"timestamp":" 947161027801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161030451","data":{"timestamp":" 947161030451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161031992","data":{"timestamp":" 947161031991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" AKAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161033203","data":{"timestamp":" 947161033202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161033514","data":{"timestamp":" 947161033513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161034535","data":{"timestamp":" 947161034535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIVUNO"," userResponse":" MAJIVUNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161035469","data":{"timestamp":" 947161035468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161036449","data":{"timestamp":" 947161036448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161036682","data":{"timestamp":" 947161036682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161037152","data":{"timestamp":" 947161037152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161037877","data":{"timestamp":" 947161037876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161038407","data":{"timestamp":" 947161038406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161040142","data":{"timestamp":" 947161040142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161040678","data":{"timestamp":" 947161040678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161041537","data":{"timestamp":" 947161041536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161041789","data":{"timestamp":" 947161041789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161042831","data":{"timestamp":" 947161042830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAIVA"," userResponse":" KITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161044211","data":{"timestamp":" 947161044211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161046201","data":{"timestamp":" 947161046201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161046749","data":{"timestamp":" 947161046749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161047574","data":{"timestamp":" 947161047573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161048482","data":{"timestamp":" 947161048481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161048988","data":{"timestamp":" 947161048987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161050509","data":{"timestamp":" 947161050509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUTWA"," userResponse":" UMEVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161053097","data":{"timestamp":" 947161053096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161053576","data":{"timestamp":" 947161053575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161054991","data":{"timestamp":" 947161054991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161055396","data":{"timestamp":" 947161055396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161055846","data":{"timestamp":" 947161055845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161056175","data":{"timestamp":" 947161056174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161057172","data":{"timestamp":" 947161057171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161058563","data":{"timestamp":" 947161058563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161059636","data":{"timestamp":" 947161059635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161060354","data":{"timestamp":" 947161060354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161060580","data":{"timestamp":" 947161060579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161061352","data":{"timestamp":" 947161061352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161061624","data":{"timestamp":" 947161061624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161062236","data":{"timestamp":" 947161062235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161062460","data":{"timestamp":" 947161062459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161063363","data":{"timestamp":" 947161063362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161066410","data":{"timestamp":" 947161066409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161067002","data":{"timestamp":" 947161067001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUTO"," userResponse":" MVUTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161067852","data":{"timestamp":" 947161067851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161068768","data":{"timestamp":" 947161068767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161069696","data":{"timestamp":" 947161069695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161072409","data":{"timestamp":" 947161072409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161073600","data":{"timestamp":" 947161073599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161074141","data":{"timestamp":" 947161074140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDE"," userResponse":" PANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161075044","data":{"timestamp":" 947161075044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161075967","data":{"timestamp":" 947161075966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161076615","data":{"timestamp":" 947161076614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161077325","data":{"timestamp":" 947161077325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161079579","data":{"timestamp":" 947161079579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161080713","data":{"timestamp":" 947161080712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMANI"," userResponse":" JAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161081904","data":{"timestamp":" 947161081903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161082938","data":{"timestamp":" 947161082938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161083795","data":{"timestamp":" 947161083794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161084146","data":{"timestamp":" 947161084146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161085011","data":{"timestamp":" 947161085010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161085283","data":{"timestamp":" 947161085283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161085824","data":{"timestamp":" 947161085824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161086041","data":{"timestamp":" 947161086040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161086652","data":{"timestamp":" 947161086652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161089285","data":{"timestamp":" 947161089285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161089924","data":{"timestamp":" 947161089924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161090408","data":{"timestamp":" 947161090408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161091725","data":{"timestamp":" 947161091724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161092235","data":{"timestamp":" 947161092235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161092455","data":{"timestamp":" 947161092454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161093136","data":{"timestamp":" 947161093135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161094194","data":{"timestamp":" 947161094194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAVUTWA"," userResponse":" INAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161094906","data":{"timestamp":" 947161094906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161095127","data":{"timestamp":" 947161095126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161095780","data":{"timestamp":" 947161095780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161096674","data":{"timestamp":" 947161096674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161096946","data":{"timestamp":" 947161096946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161097681","data":{"timestamp":" 947161097681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161098494","data":{"timestamp":" 947161098493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161098777","data":{"timestamp":" 947161098776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161099521","data":{"timestamp":" 947161099520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161102099","data":{"timestamp":" 947161102098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161103388","data":{"timestamp":" 947161103387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161104278","data":{"timestamp":" 947161104277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161104645","data":{"timestamp":" 947161104645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161105168","data":{"timestamp":" 947161105167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161105983","data":{"timestamp":" 947161105983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161106261","data":{"timestamp":" 947161106260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161108935","data":{"timestamp":" 947161108934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161109421","data":{"timestamp":" 947161109420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161110407","data":{"timestamp":" 947161110406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" AKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161110874","data":{"timestamp":" 947161110873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161111577","data":{"timestamp":" 947161111577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161112166","data":{"timestamp":" 947161112165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161112765","data":{"timestamp":" 947161112764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161113689","data":{"timestamp":" 947161113688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161116181","data":{"timestamp":" 947161116180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161116721","data":{"timestamp":" 947161116720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161117982","data":{"timestamp":" 947161117981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTWA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161118777","data":{"timestamp":" 947161118777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161120011","data":{"timestamp":" 947161120011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161120372","data":{"timestamp":" 947161120371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161121630","data":{"timestamp":" 947161121630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161124971","data":{"timestamp":" 947161124970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161126504","data":{"timestamp":" 947161126503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIRUSHA"," userResponse":" AKAJIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161127053","data":{"timestamp":" 947161127051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161127674","data":{"timestamp":" 947161127673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161130500","data":{"timestamp":" 947161130499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161131096","data":{"timestamp":" 947161131095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANDO"," userResponse":" TANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161131671","data":{"timestamp":" 947161131670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161133000","data":{"timestamp":" 947161133000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161133278","data":{"timestamp":" 947161133277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161134152","data":{"timestamp":" 947161134151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161135894","data":{"timestamp":" 947161135894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIVUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161137508","data":{"timestamp":" 947161137508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161138175","data":{"timestamp":" 947161138175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161139813","data":{"timestamp":" 947161139812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161140896","data":{"timestamp":" 947161140896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161141437","data":{"timestamp":" 947161141437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161142323","data":{"timestamp":" 947161142322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UFUKWE"," userResponse":" UFUKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161144728","data":{"timestamp":" 947161144727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161146397","data":{"timestamp":" 947161146397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAHEMA"," userResponse":" AKAHEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161147258","data":{"timestamp":" 947161147257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161148461","data":{"timestamp":" 947161148460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJONZI"," userResponse":" MAJONZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161149467","data":{"timestamp":" 947161149467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161150302","data":{"timestamp":" 947161150301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161151156","data":{"timestamp":" 947161151155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161151947","data":{"timestamp":" 947161151946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161153179","data":{"timestamp":" 947161153178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGINE"," userResponse":" PENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161153806","data":{"timestamp":" 947161153806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161154879","data":{"timestamp":" 947161154879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161155521","data":{"timestamp":" 947161155521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161156104","data":{"timestamp":" 947161156103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161156830","data":{"timestamp":" 947161156830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161158993","data":{"timestamp":" 947161158992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161159648","data":{"timestamp":" 947161159647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161160244","data":{"timestamp":" 947161160244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161161636","data":{"timestamp":" 947161161635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161162828","data":{"timestamp":" 947161162827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161163601","data":{"timestamp":" 947161163600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161164259","data":{"timestamp":" 947161164259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161165387","data":{"timestamp":" 947161165386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINANE"," userResponse":" MINANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161166900","data":{"timestamp":" 947161166900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161168046","data":{"timestamp":" 947161168045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161170203","data":{"timestamp":" 947161170203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161171157","data":{"timestamp":" 947161171157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161171902","data":{"timestamp":" 947161171902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161173013","data":{"timestamp":" 947161173013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161173788","data":{"timestamp":" 947161173787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161174602","data":{"timestamp":" 947161174601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161177379","data":{"timestamp":" 947161177377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161177471","data":{"timestamp":" 947161177471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" cea866d1-622b-413a-8b54-7739e7b30137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161216161","data":{"timestamp":" 947161216161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161216785","data":{"timestamp":" 947161216785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161217028","data":{"timestamp":" 947161217028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161217584","data":{"timestamp":" 947161217584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161218743","data":{"timestamp":" 947161218742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161219510","data":{"timestamp":" 947161219509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161220914","data":{"timestamp":" 947161220914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161221810","data":{"timestamp":" 947161221810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161222448","data":{"timestamp":" 947161222447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161223386","data":{"timestamp":" 947161223386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161224034","data":{"timestamp":" 947161224033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161226478","data":{"timestamp":" 947161226477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161226727","data":{"timestamp":" 947161226726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161227660","data":{"timestamp":" 947161227659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161228533","data":{"timestamp":" 947161228533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161229367","data":{"timestamp":" 947161229367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161230261","data":{"timestamp":" 947161230260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161232998","data":{"timestamp":" 947161232998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161233425","data":{"timestamp":" 947161233424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161234118","data":{"timestamp":" 947161234118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161235162","data":{"timestamp":" 947161235162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161236101","data":{"timestamp":" 947161236101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161236916","data":{"timestamp":" 947161236916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161237850","data":{"timestamp":" 947161237850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161239471","data":{"timestamp":" 947161239471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161239676","data":{"timestamp":" 947161239676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161240522","data":{"timestamp":" 947161240521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161241217","data":{"timestamp":" 947161241217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161241511","data":{"timestamp":" 947161241511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161242376","data":{"timestamp":" 947161242376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161243450","data":{"timestamp":" 947161243449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161246570","data":{"timestamp":" 947161246569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161247186","data":{"timestamp":" 947161247185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161248280","data":{"timestamp":" 947161248280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161249414","data":{"timestamp":" 947161249414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161249759","data":{"timestamp":" 947161249758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161250623","data":{"timestamp":" 947161250623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161251860","data":{"timestamp":" 947161251860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161252699","data":{"timestamp":" 947161252699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161255391","data":{"timestamp":" 947161255391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161256292","data":{"timestamp":" 947161256291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161256860","data":{"timestamp":" 947161256860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161257094","data":{"timestamp":" 947161257094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161257808","data":{"timestamp":" 947161257808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161258613","data":{"timestamp":" 947161258613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161261329","data":{"timestamp":" 947161261328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161262325","data":{"timestamp":" 947161262325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161262807","data":{"timestamp":" 947161262806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161263061","data":{"timestamp":" 947161263061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161263855","data":{"timestamp":" 947161263854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161265144","data":{"timestamp":" 947161265144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161265459","data":{"timestamp":" 947161265459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161266684","data":{"timestamp":" 947161266684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161267589","data":{"timestamp":" 947161267589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161268251","data":{"timestamp":" 947161268250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161268503","data":{"timestamp":" 947161268502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161269364","data":{"timestamp":" 947161269364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161269906","data":{"timestamp":" 947161269906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161270473","data":{"timestamp":" 947161270473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161271048","data":{"timestamp":" 947161271048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161273820","data":{"timestamp":" 947161273820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161275074","data":{"timestamp":" 947161275074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161276078","data":{"timestamp":" 947161276078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161277243","data":{"timestamp":" 947161277243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 928c44bf-ea3a-40cb-8ca3-d111e81182ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161297857","data":{"timestamp":" 947161297856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161298494","data":{"timestamp":" 947161298493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161298749","data":{"timestamp":" 947161298749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161299318","data":{"timestamp":" 947161299318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161300479","data":{"timestamp":" 947161300478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161301251","data":{"timestamp":" 947161301250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161302669","data":{"timestamp":" 947161302668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161303571","data":{"timestamp":" 947161303570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161304212","data":{"timestamp":" 947161304212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161305155","data":{"timestamp":" 947161305155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161305809","data":{"timestamp":" 947161305809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161308247","data":{"timestamp":" 947161308247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161308499","data":{"timestamp":" 947161308498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161309435","data":{"timestamp":" 947161309434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161310308","data":{"timestamp":" 947161310308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161311142","data":{"timestamp":" 947161311142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161312050","data":{"timestamp":" 947161312049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161314825","data":{"timestamp":" 947161314824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161315260","data":{"timestamp":" 947161315259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161315971","data":{"timestamp":" 947161315971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161317033","data":{"timestamp":" 947161317031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161317971","data":{"timestamp":" 947161317970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161318805","data":{"timestamp":" 947161318804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161319753","data":{"timestamp":" 947161319752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161321360","data":{"timestamp":" 947161321360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161321566","data":{"timestamp":" 947161321566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161322421","data":{"timestamp":" 947161322421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161323116","data":{"timestamp":" 947161323116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161323411","data":{"timestamp":" 947161323411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161324291","data":{"timestamp":" 947161324290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161325347","data":{"timestamp":" 947161325347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161327173","data":{"timestamp":" 947161327172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161327240","data":{"timestamp":" 947161327239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 5f6b3f36-a251-4a6b-be69-3ed8404bad11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161341201","data":{"timestamp":" 947161341201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161341838","data":{"timestamp":" 947161341837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161342092","data":{"timestamp":" 947161342091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161342663","data":{"timestamp":" 947161342662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161343810","data":{"timestamp":" 947161343810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161344570","data":{"timestamp":" 947161344569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161345991","data":{"timestamp":" 947161345991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161346876","data":{"timestamp":" 947161346875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161347514","data":{"timestamp":" 947161347513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161348451","data":{"timestamp":" 947161348451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161349096","data":{"timestamp":" 947161349096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161351481","data":{"timestamp":" 947161351480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161351731","data":{"timestamp":" 947161351731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161352659","data":{"timestamp":" 947161352659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161353534","data":{"timestamp":" 947161353534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161354384","data":{"timestamp":" 947161354384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161355288","data":{"timestamp":" 947161355288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161358078","data":{"timestamp":" 947161358078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161358501","data":{"timestamp":" 947161358501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161359217","data":{"timestamp":" 947161359217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161360278","data":{"timestamp":" 947161360277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161361205","data":{"timestamp":" 947161361205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161362018","data":{"timestamp":" 947161362018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161362953","data":{"timestamp":" 947161362953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161364557","data":{"timestamp":" 947161364556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161364752","data":{"timestamp":" 947161364752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161365599","data":{"timestamp":" 947161365599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161366294","data":{"timestamp":" 947161366294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161366595","data":{"timestamp":" 947161366595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161367460","data":{"timestamp":" 947161367459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161368515","data":{"timestamp":" 947161368515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161371703","data":{"timestamp":" 947161371702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161372318","data":{"timestamp":" 947161372318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161373413","data":{"timestamp":" 947161373412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161374563","data":{"timestamp":" 947161374562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161374919","data":{"timestamp":" 947161374919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161375800","data":{"timestamp":" 947161375799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161377024","data":{"timestamp":" 947161377024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161377849","data":{"timestamp":" 947161377849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161380485","data":{"timestamp":" 947161380485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161381383","data":{"timestamp":" 947161381382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161381947","data":{"timestamp":" 947161381947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161382181","data":{"timestamp":" 947161382181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161382895","data":{"timestamp":" 947161382895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161383700","data":{"timestamp":" 947161383699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161386387","data":{"timestamp":" 947161386385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161387392","data":{"timestamp":" 947161387391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161387879","data":{"timestamp":" 947161387879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161388152","data":{"timestamp":" 947161388152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161388944","data":{"timestamp":" 947161388944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161390245","data":{"timestamp":" 947161390245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161390576","data":{"timestamp":" 947161390576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161391801","data":{"timestamp":" 947161391801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161392706","data":{"timestamp":" 947161392706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161393351","data":{"timestamp":" 947161393351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161393586","data":{"timestamp":" 947161393586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161394431","data":{"timestamp":" 947161394431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161394956","data":{"timestamp":" 947161394956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161395522","data":{"timestamp":" 947161395522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161396077","data":{"timestamp":" 947161396077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161398928","data":{"timestamp":" 947161398928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161400183","data":{"timestamp":" 947161400183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161401187","data":{"timestamp":" 947161401187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161402531","data":{"timestamp":" 947161402531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161403565","data":{"timestamp":" 947161403565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161404090","data":{"timestamp":" 947161404090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161405235","data":{"timestamp":" 947161405235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161406687","data":{"timestamp":" 947161406686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161407834","data":{"timestamp":" 947161407834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161408388","data":{"timestamp":" 947161408388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161409349","data":{"timestamp":" 947161409348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161411970","data":{"timestamp":" 947161411969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161412953","data":{"timestamp":" 947161412952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161413260","data":{"timestamp":" 947161413259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161414031","data":{"timestamp":" 947161414031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161415407","data":{"timestamp":" 947161415406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161416078","data":{"timestamp":" 947161416077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161416496","data":{"timestamp":" 947161416495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161417351","data":{"timestamp":" 947161417351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161418391","data":{"timestamp":" 947161418390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161418874","data":{"timestamp":" 947161418873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161419827","data":{"timestamp":" 947161419827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161420025","data":{"timestamp":" 947161420025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161420807","data":{"timestamp":" 947161420807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161423501","data":{"timestamp":" 947161423501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161424508","data":{"timestamp":" 947161424508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161425483","data":{"timestamp":" 947161425482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161426715","data":{"timestamp":" 947161426714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161427356","data":{"timestamp":" 947161427355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161428507","data":{"timestamp":" 947161428506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161429341","data":{"timestamp":" 947161429340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161430092","data":{"timestamp":" 947161430092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161430259","data":{"timestamp":" 947161430258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161431028","data":{"timestamp":" 947161431028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161434230","data":{"timestamp":" 947161434229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161435522","data":{"timestamp":" 947161435521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161436356","data":{"timestamp":" 947161436356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161438539","data":{"timestamp":" 947161438539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161439406","data":{"timestamp":" 947161439406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161440642","data":{"timestamp":" 947161440642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161441323","data":{"timestamp":" 947161441323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161441877","data":{"timestamp":" 947161441877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161442502","data":{"timestamp":" 947161442502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161443533","data":{"timestamp":" 947161443533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161443930","data":{"timestamp":" 947161443930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161444663","data":{"timestamp":" 947161444663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161445164","data":{"timestamp":" 947161445163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161445624","data":{"timestamp":" 947161445624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161446246","data":{"timestamp":" 947161446245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161448715","data":{"timestamp":" 947161448715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161450401","data":{"timestamp":" 947161450401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161451555","data":{"timestamp":" 947161451554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161452335","data":{"timestamp":" 947161452334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161452819","data":{"timestamp":" 947161452819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161453900","data":{"timestamp":" 947161453899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161454470","data":{"timestamp":" 947161454470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161457074","data":{"timestamp":" 947161457074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161457992","data":{"timestamp":" 947161457991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161458712","data":{"timestamp":" 947161458711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161458893","data":{"timestamp":" 947161458893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161459420","data":{"timestamp":" 947161459419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161460158","data":{"timestamp":" 947161460157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161460729","data":{"timestamp":" 947161460728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161463667","data":{"timestamp":" 947161463667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161464294","data":{"timestamp":" 947161464294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161467590","data":{"timestamp":" 947161467589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161468994","data":{"timestamp":" 947161468993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161469280","data":{"timestamp":" 947161469280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161470135","data":{"timestamp":" 947161470135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161471404","data":{"timestamp":" 947161471404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161472285","data":{"timestamp":" 947161472285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161472380","data":{"timestamp":" 947161472380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161472728","data":{"timestamp":" 947161472727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161473791","data":{"timestamp":" 947161473791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161474741","data":{"timestamp":" 947161474740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161476743","data":{"timestamp":" 947161476742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161477513","data":{"timestamp":" 947161477512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161477614","data":{"timestamp":" 947161477614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" bf563bdd-9d7d-4e51-bdb6-dc7760e67a6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161493380","data":{"timestamp":" 947161493379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161494019","data":{"timestamp":" 947161494018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161494274","data":{"timestamp":" 947161494273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161494840","data":{"timestamp":" 947161494839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161495997","data":{"timestamp":" 947161495997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161496762","data":{"timestamp":" 947161496761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161498183","data":{"timestamp":" 947161498182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161499085","data":{"timestamp":" 947161499084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161499725","data":{"timestamp":" 947161499724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161500649","data":{"timestamp":" 947161500649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161501287","data":{"timestamp":" 947161501286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161503693","data":{"timestamp":" 947161503692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161503945","data":{"timestamp":" 947161503943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161504878","data":{"timestamp":" 947161504877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161505771","data":{"timestamp":" 947161505770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161506618","data":{"timestamp":" 947161506617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161507526","data":{"timestamp":" 947161507525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161510278","data":{"timestamp":" 947161510278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161510717","data":{"timestamp":" 947161510717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161511427","data":{"timestamp":" 947161511426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161512488","data":{"timestamp":" 947161512487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161513431","data":{"timestamp":" 947161513430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161514262","data":{"timestamp":" 947161514261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161515212","data":{"timestamp":" 947161515211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161516837","data":{"timestamp":" 947161516836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161517052","data":{"timestamp":" 947161517052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161517910","data":{"timestamp":" 947161517909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161518626","data":{"timestamp":" 947161518625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161518946","data":{"timestamp":" 947161518946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161519827","data":{"timestamp":" 947161519827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161520907","data":{"timestamp":" 947161520906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161523934","data":{"timestamp":" 947161523933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161524555","data":{"timestamp":" 947161524554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161525664","data":{"timestamp":" 947161525663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161526814","data":{"timestamp":" 947161526814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161527173","data":{"timestamp":" 947161527172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161528053","data":{"timestamp":" 947161528053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161529294","data":{"timestamp":" 947161529293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161530130","data":{"timestamp":" 947161530129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161532758","data":{"timestamp":" 947161532757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161533652","data":{"timestamp":" 947161533652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161534231","data":{"timestamp":" 947161534231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161534477","data":{"timestamp":" 947161534476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161535212","data":{"timestamp":" 947161535211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161536032","data":{"timestamp":" 947161536031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161538729","data":{"timestamp":" 947161538728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161539728","data":{"timestamp":" 947161539727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161540204","data":{"timestamp":" 947161540203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161540471","data":{"timestamp":" 947161540470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161541258","data":{"timestamp":" 947161541258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161542567","data":{"timestamp":" 947161542567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161542893","data":{"timestamp":" 947161542893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161544137","data":{"timestamp":" 947161544136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161545058","data":{"timestamp":" 947161545058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161545725","data":{"timestamp":" 947161545724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161545979","data":{"timestamp":" 947161545979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161546841","data":{"timestamp":" 947161546841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161547390","data":{"timestamp":" 947161547389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161547969","data":{"timestamp":" 947161547969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161548537","data":{"timestamp":" 947161548536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161551331","data":{"timestamp":" 947161551330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161552598","data":{"timestamp":" 947161552597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161553615","data":{"timestamp":" 947161553615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161554978","data":{"timestamp":" 947161554977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161556027","data":{"timestamp":" 947161556026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161556572","data":{"timestamp":" 947161556569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161557735","data":{"timestamp":" 947161557734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161559188","data":{"timestamp":" 947161559187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161560327","data":{"timestamp":" 947161560326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161560878","data":{"timestamp":" 947161560877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161561841","data":{"timestamp":" 947161561840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161564403","data":{"timestamp":" 947161564402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161565386","data":{"timestamp":" 947161565386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161565698","data":{"timestamp":" 947161565698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161566468","data":{"timestamp":" 947161566467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161567840","data":{"timestamp":" 947161567839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161568522","data":{"timestamp":" 947161568522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161568954","data":{"timestamp":" 947161568953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161569808","data":{"timestamp":" 947161569808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161570850","data":{"timestamp":" 947161570850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161571330","data":{"timestamp":" 947161571330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161572282","data":{"timestamp":" 947161572282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161572489","data":{"timestamp":" 947161572486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161573281","data":{"timestamp":" 947161573278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161575910","data":{"timestamp":" 947161575909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161576920","data":{"timestamp":" 947161576920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161577887","data":{"timestamp":" 947161577887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161579119","data":{"timestamp":" 947161579118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161579755","data":{"timestamp":" 947161579755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161580907","data":{"timestamp":" 947161580907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161581740","data":{"timestamp":" 947161581740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161582490","data":{"timestamp":" 947161582489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161582651","data":{"timestamp":" 947161582651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161583422","data":{"timestamp":" 947161583421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161586622","data":{"timestamp":" 947161586621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161587911","data":{"timestamp":" 947161587910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161588756","data":{"timestamp":" 947161588756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161590960","data":{"timestamp":" 947161590959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161591841","data":{"timestamp":" 947161591840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161593078","data":{"timestamp":" 947161593078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161593770","data":{"timestamp":" 947161593770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161594343","data":{"timestamp":" 947161594342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161594985","data":{"timestamp":" 947161594984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161596017","data":{"timestamp":" 947161596017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161596417","data":{"timestamp":" 947161596417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161597151","data":{"timestamp":" 947161597150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161597654","data":{"timestamp":" 947161597653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161598116","data":{"timestamp":" 947161598116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161598741","data":{"timestamp":" 947161598740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161601068","data":{"timestamp":" 947161601068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161602755","data":{"timestamp":" 947161602754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161603914","data":{"timestamp":" 947161603913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161604693","data":{"timestamp":" 947161604692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161605169","data":{"timestamp":" 947161605168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161606253","data":{"timestamp":" 947161606252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161606823","data":{"timestamp":" 947161606822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161609511","data":{"timestamp":" 947161609510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161610424","data":{"timestamp":" 947161610423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161611143","data":{"timestamp":" 947161611142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161611329","data":{"timestamp":" 947161611329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161611857","data":{"timestamp":" 947161611856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161612585","data":{"timestamp":" 947161612584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161613161","data":{"timestamp":" 947161613160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161616128","data":{"timestamp":" 947161616127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161616756","data":{"timestamp":" 947161616756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161620044","data":{"timestamp":" 947161620044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161621440","data":{"timestamp":" 947161621440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161621732","data":{"timestamp":" 947161621732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161622599","data":{"timestamp":" 947161622598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161623872","data":{"timestamp":" 947161623871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161624756","data":{"timestamp":" 947161624755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161624858","data":{"timestamp":" 947161624857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161625211","data":{"timestamp":" 947161625211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161626276","data":{"timestamp":" 947161626276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161627232","data":{"timestamp":" 947161627231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161629224","data":{"timestamp":" 947161629224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161630086","data":{"timestamp":" 947161630086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161630191","data":{"timestamp":" 947161630191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161631187","data":{"timestamp":" 947161631186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161632661","data":{"timestamp":" 947161632661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161633729","data":{"timestamp":" 947161633729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161635291","data":{"timestamp":" 947161635291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161635840","data":{"timestamp":" 947161635840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161636594","data":{"timestamp":" 947161636593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161639576","data":{"timestamp":" 947161639575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161640817","data":{"timestamp":" 947161640816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161641628","data":{"timestamp":" 947161641628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161642739","data":{"timestamp":" 947161642738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161643334","data":{"timestamp":" 947161643334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161644316","data":{"timestamp":" 947161644316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161645177","data":{"timestamp":" 947161645177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161646299","data":{"timestamp":" 947161646298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161647400","data":{"timestamp":" 947161647399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161650133","data":{"timestamp":" 947161650132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161651151","data":{"timestamp":" 947161651150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161652852","data":{"timestamp":" 947161652851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161653495","data":{"timestamp":" 947161653495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161653902","data":{"timestamp":" 947161653902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161654729","data":{"timestamp":" 947161654729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161657556","data":{"timestamp":" 947161657556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161658746","data":{"timestamp":" 947161658746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161659357","data":{"timestamp":" 947161659356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161660207","data":{"timestamp":" 947161660207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161661499","data":{"timestamp":" 947161661499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161662381","data":{"timestamp":" 947161662380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161663511","data":{"timestamp":" 947161663511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161664002","data":{"timestamp":" 947161664001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161664614","data":{"timestamp":" 947161664613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161665500","data":{"timestamp":" 947161665499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161666150","data":{"timestamp":" 947161666149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161666814","data":{"timestamp":" 947161666813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161667336","data":{"timestamp":" 947161667335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161668089","data":{"timestamp":" 947161668089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161668569","data":{"timestamp":" 947161668569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161669099","data":{"timestamp":" 947161669099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161670085","data":{"timestamp":" 947161670084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161670356","data":{"timestamp":" 947161670355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161671241","data":{"timestamp":" 947161671241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161673273","data":{"timestamp":" 947161673273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161674117","data":{"timestamp":" 947161674117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161675055","data":{"timestamp":" 947161675055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161675679","data":{"timestamp":" 947161675678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161675906","data":{"timestamp":" 947161675905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161676839","data":{"timestamp":" 947161676838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161677991","data":{"timestamp":" 947161677991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161678543","data":{"timestamp":" 947161678542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161679344","data":{"timestamp":" 947161679344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161680131","data":{"timestamp":" 947161680130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161680721","data":{"timestamp":" 947161680721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161681568","data":{"timestamp":" 947161681568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161682451","data":{"timestamp":" 947161682450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161683303","data":{"timestamp":" 947161683302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161684016","data":{"timestamp":" 947161684016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161686116","data":{"timestamp":" 947161686115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161686675","data":{"timestamp":" 947161686674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161687672","data":{"timestamp":" 947161687672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161688361","data":{"timestamp":" 947161688360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161691601","data":{"timestamp":" 947161691600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161692976","data":{"timestamp":" 947161692976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161693221","data":{"timestamp":" 947161693220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161693620","data":{"timestamp":" 947161693620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161694465","data":{"timestamp":" 947161694464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161695799","data":{"timestamp":" 947161695799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161697415","data":{"timestamp":" 947161697415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161697662","data":{"timestamp":" 947161697661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161698739","data":{"timestamp":" 947161698739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161700339","data":{"timestamp":" 947161700338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161701852","data":{"timestamp":" 947161701851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161702644","data":{"timestamp":" 947161702644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161702750","data":{"timestamp":" 947161702750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161703424","data":{"timestamp":" 947161703424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161704321","data":{"timestamp":" 947161704321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161706371","data":{"timestamp":" 947161706370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161706615","data":{"timestamp":" 947161706615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161707345","data":{"timestamp":" 947161707345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161708258","data":{"timestamp":" 947161708258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161708479","data":{"timestamp":" 947161708479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161709726","data":{"timestamp":" 947161709725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161712241","data":{"timestamp":" 947161712241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161712658","data":{"timestamp":" 947161712658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161713362","data":{"timestamp":" 947161713362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161714285","data":{"timestamp":" 947161714285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161715313","data":{"timestamp":" 947161715313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161716520","data":{"timestamp":" 947161716519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161717202","data":{"timestamp":" 947161717202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161718397","data":{"timestamp":" 947161718397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161719040","data":{"timestamp":" 947161719040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161719872","data":{"timestamp":" 947161719871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161720031","data":{"timestamp":" 947161720031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161721061","data":{"timestamp":" 947161721060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161723325","data":{"timestamp":" 947161723325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161723843","data":{"timestamp":" 947161723842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161724674","data":{"timestamp":" 947161724673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161727685","data":{"timestamp":" 947161727684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161728399","data":{"timestamp":" 947161728399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161729018","data":{"timestamp":" 947161729017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161729876","data":{"timestamp":" 947161729876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161730915","data":{"timestamp":" 947161730914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161733152","data":{"timestamp":" 947161733152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161733609","data":{"timestamp":" 947161733608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161734606","data":{"timestamp":" 947161734606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161735770","data":{"timestamp":" 947161735770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161736923","data":{"timestamp":" 947161736923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161737716","data":{"timestamp":" 947161737715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161739229","data":{"timestamp":" 947161739228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161740145","data":{"timestamp":" 947161740145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161741476","data":{"timestamp":" 947161741476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161742014","data":{"timestamp":" 947161742013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161742637","data":{"timestamp":" 947161742637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161743501","data":{"timestamp":" 947161743500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161744336","data":{"timestamp":" 947161744336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161744979","data":{"timestamp":" 947161744978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161745552","data":{"timestamp":" 947161745551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161746323","data":{"timestamp":" 947161746322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161746845","data":{"timestamp":" 947161746845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161747442","data":{"timestamp":" 947161747441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161747655","data":{"timestamp":" 947161747654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161748348","data":{"timestamp":" 947161748348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161749199","data":{"timestamp":" 947161749198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161751629","data":{"timestamp":" 947161751629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161752006","data":{"timestamp":" 947161752006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161752667","data":{"timestamp":" 947161752666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161753455","data":{"timestamp":" 947161753454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161753704","data":{"timestamp":" 947161753703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161754198","data":{"timestamp":" 947161754197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161755017","data":{"timestamp":" 947161755017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161755797","data":{"timestamp":" 947161755796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161756861","data":{"timestamp":" 947161756861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161757460","data":{"timestamp":" 947161757458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161760803","data":{"timestamp":" 947161760802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161761565","data":{"timestamp":" 947161761564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161762550","data":{"timestamp":" 947161762550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161763431","data":{"timestamp":" 947161763431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161764495","data":{"timestamp":" 947161764494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161764993","data":{"timestamp":" 947161764992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161766070","data":{"timestamp":" 947161766069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161767240","data":{"timestamp":" 947161767239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161768608","data":{"timestamp":" 947161768604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161768963","data":{"timestamp":" 947161768962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161769657","data":{"timestamp":" 947161769657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161769959","data":{"timestamp":" 947161769959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161771006","data":{"timestamp":" 947161771005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161773645","data":{"timestamp":" 947161773644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161775176","data":{"timestamp":" 947161775175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" AKAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161776385","data":{"timestamp":" 947161776384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161776690","data":{"timestamp":" 947161776690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161777711","data":{"timestamp":" 947161777710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIVUNO"," userResponse":" MAJIVUNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161778638","data":{"timestamp":" 947161778638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161779620","data":{"timestamp":" 947161779619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161779849","data":{"timestamp":" 947161779848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161780328","data":{"timestamp":" 947161780328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161781059","data":{"timestamp":" 947161781058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161781594","data":{"timestamp":" 947161781593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161783346","data":{"timestamp":" 947161783346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161783895","data":{"timestamp":" 947161783895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161784761","data":{"timestamp":" 947161784760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161785015","data":{"timestamp":" 947161785015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161786049","data":{"timestamp":" 947161786049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAIVA"," userResponse":" KITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161787433","data":{"timestamp":" 947161787433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161789420","data":{"timestamp":" 947161789419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161789965","data":{"timestamp":" 947161789964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161790796","data":{"timestamp":" 947161790796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161791709","data":{"timestamp":" 947161791708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161792219","data":{"timestamp":" 947161792218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161793741","data":{"timestamp":" 947161793740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUTWA"," userResponse":" UMEVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161796346","data":{"timestamp":" 947161796345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161796822","data":{"timestamp":" 947161796821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161798239","data":{"timestamp":" 947161798238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161798643","data":{"timestamp":" 947161798642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161799090","data":{"timestamp":" 947161799090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161799423","data":{"timestamp":" 947161799423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161800411","data":{"timestamp":" 947161800411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161801807","data":{"timestamp":" 947161801806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161802879","data":{"timestamp":" 947161802879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161803604","data":{"timestamp":" 947161803603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161803836","data":{"timestamp":" 947161803835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161804611","data":{"timestamp":" 947161804610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161804884","data":{"timestamp":" 947161804883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161805501","data":{"timestamp":" 947161805501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161805718","data":{"timestamp":" 947161805718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161806623","data":{"timestamp":" 947161806623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161809604","data":{"timestamp":" 947161809603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161810193","data":{"timestamp":" 947161810192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUTO"," userResponse":" MVUTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161811043","data":{"timestamp":" 947161811042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161811968","data":{"timestamp":" 947161811968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161812898","data":{"timestamp":" 947161812897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161815717","data":{"timestamp":" 947161815717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161816905","data":{"timestamp":" 947161816905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161817430","data":{"timestamp":" 947161817430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDE"," userResponse":" PANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161818314","data":{"timestamp":" 947161818314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161819218","data":{"timestamp":" 947161819218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161819852","data":{"timestamp":" 947161819852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161820552","data":{"timestamp":" 947161820551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161822778","data":{"timestamp":" 947161822778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161823918","data":{"timestamp":" 947161823917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMANI"," userResponse":" JAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161825093","data":{"timestamp":" 947161825092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161826128","data":{"timestamp":" 947161826128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161826972","data":{"timestamp":" 947161826972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161827307","data":{"timestamp":" 947161827307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161828152","data":{"timestamp":" 947161828152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161828406","data":{"timestamp":" 947161828406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161828939","data":{"timestamp":" 947161828939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161829148","data":{"timestamp":" 947161829148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161829742","data":{"timestamp":" 947161829742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161832410","data":{"timestamp":" 947161832410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161833053","data":{"timestamp":" 947161833053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161833544","data":{"timestamp":" 947161833543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161834866","data":{"timestamp":" 947161834865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161835361","data":{"timestamp":" 947161835361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161835565","data":{"timestamp":" 947161835565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161836223","data":{"timestamp":" 947161836223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161837258","data":{"timestamp":" 947161837258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAVUTWA"," userResponse":" INAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161837953","data":{"timestamp":" 947161837953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161838158","data":{"timestamp":" 947161838158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161838793","data":{"timestamp":" 947161838793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161839669","data":{"timestamp":" 947161839669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161839925","data":{"timestamp":" 947161839925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161840641","data":{"timestamp":" 947161840641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161841436","data":{"timestamp":" 947161841436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161841701","data":{"timestamp":" 947161841701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161842437","data":{"timestamp":" 947161842436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161845165","data":{"timestamp":" 947161845164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161846456","data":{"timestamp":" 947161846456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161847340","data":{"timestamp":" 947161847339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161847707","data":{"timestamp":" 947161847707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161848226","data":{"timestamp":" 947161848225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161849041","data":{"timestamp":" 947161849041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161849317","data":{"timestamp":" 947161849316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161851912","data":{"timestamp":" 947161851911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161852399","data":{"timestamp":" 947161852398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161853381","data":{"timestamp":" 947161853380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" AKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161853850","data":{"timestamp":" 947161853849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161854550","data":{"timestamp":" 947161854549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161855131","data":{"timestamp":" 947161855130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161855733","data":{"timestamp":" 947161855732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161856653","data":{"timestamp":" 947161856653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161859190","data":{"timestamp":" 947161859190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161859726","data":{"timestamp":" 947161859725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161860970","data":{"timestamp":" 947161860970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTWA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161861784","data":{"timestamp":" 947161861783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161863007","data":{"timestamp":" 947161863007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161863375","data":{"timestamp":" 947161863375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161864620","data":{"timestamp":" 947161864620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161868005","data":{"timestamp":" 947161868004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161869538","data":{"timestamp":" 947161869538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIRUSHA"," userResponse":" AKAJIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161870089","data":{"timestamp":" 947161870088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161870707","data":{"timestamp":" 947161870707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161873466","data":{"timestamp":" 947161873465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161874051","data":{"timestamp":" 947161874051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANDO"," userResponse":" TANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161874631","data":{"timestamp":" 947161874630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161875960","data":{"timestamp":" 947161875959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161876236","data":{"timestamp":" 947161876236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161877109","data":{"timestamp":" 947161877108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161878853","data":{"timestamp":" 947161878852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIVUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161880464","data":{"timestamp":" 947161880463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161881115","data":{"timestamp":" 947161881115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161882749","data":{"timestamp":" 947161882749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161883833","data":{"timestamp":" 947161883832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161884374","data":{"timestamp":" 947161884374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161885254","data":{"timestamp":" 947161885253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UFUKWE"," userResponse":" UFUKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161887760","data":{"timestamp":" 947161887759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161889429","data":{"timestamp":" 947161889428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAHEMA"," userResponse":" AKAHEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161890291","data":{"timestamp":" 947161890290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161891503","data":{"timestamp":" 947161891503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJONZI"," userResponse":" MAJONZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161892495","data":{"timestamp":" 947161892494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161893329","data":{"timestamp":" 947161893328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161894180","data":{"timestamp":" 947161894179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161894972","data":{"timestamp":" 947161894971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161896204","data":{"timestamp":" 947161896203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGINE"," userResponse":" PENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161896830","data":{"timestamp":" 947161896830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161897889","data":{"timestamp":" 947161897889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161898531","data":{"timestamp":" 947161898530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161899121","data":{"timestamp":" 947161899121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161899846","data":{"timestamp":" 947161899845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161902004","data":{"timestamp":" 947161902003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161902662","data":{"timestamp":" 947161902662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161903268","data":{"timestamp":" 947161903268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161904659","data":{"timestamp":" 947161904658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161905849","data":{"timestamp":" 947161905849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161906619","data":{"timestamp":" 947161906619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161907264","data":{"timestamp":" 947161907264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161908370","data":{"timestamp":" 947161908369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINANE"," userResponse":" MINANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161909864","data":{"timestamp":" 947161909864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161910989","data":{"timestamp":" 947161910989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161913179","data":{"timestamp":" 947161913178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161914138","data":{"timestamp":" 947161914137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161914887","data":{"timestamp":" 947161914886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161915997","data":{"timestamp":" 947161915996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161916775","data":{"timestamp":" 947161916775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161917599","data":{"timestamp":" 947161917598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161920343","data":{"timestamp":" 947161920343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161920419","data":{"timestamp":" 947161920419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 3fa4395c-648b-4bcd-9d59-5bd029d60802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161950577","data":{"timestamp":" 947161950576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161951216","data":{"timestamp":" 947161951215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161951471","data":{"timestamp":" 947161951470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161952042","data":{"timestamp":" 947161952041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161953207","data":{"timestamp":" 947161953207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161953976","data":{"timestamp":" 947161953975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161955398","data":{"timestamp":" 947161955396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161956303","data":{"timestamp":" 947161956303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161956940","data":{"timestamp":" 947161956939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161957882","data":{"timestamp":" 947161957881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161958529","data":{"timestamp":" 947161958529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161960953","data":{"timestamp":" 947161960952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161961204","data":{"timestamp":" 947161961203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161962142","data":{"timestamp":" 947161962142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161963026","data":{"timestamp":" 947161963025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161963870","data":{"timestamp":" 947161963869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161964777","data":{"timestamp":" 947161964777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161967613","data":{"timestamp":" 947161967613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161968048","data":{"timestamp":" 947161968048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161968761","data":{"timestamp":" 947161968761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161969825","data":{"timestamp":" 947161969824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161970765","data":{"timestamp":" 947161970764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161971594","data":{"timestamp":" 947161971594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161972545","data":{"timestamp":" 947161972544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161974173","data":{"timestamp":" 947161974173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161974381","data":{"timestamp":" 947161974380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161975242","data":{"timestamp":" 947161975241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161975953","data":{"timestamp":" 947161975952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161976271","data":{"timestamp":" 947161976271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161977154","data":{"timestamp":" 947161977153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161978231","data":{"timestamp":" 947161978231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161981321","data":{"timestamp":" 947161981321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161981943","data":{"timestamp":" 947161981942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161983053","data":{"timestamp":" 947161983052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161984205","data":{"timestamp":" 947161984204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161984561","data":{"timestamp":" 947161984561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161985441","data":{"timestamp":" 947161985440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161986682","data":{"timestamp":" 947161986681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161987524","data":{"timestamp":" 947161987524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161990156","data":{"timestamp":" 947161990156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161991056","data":{"timestamp":" 947161991056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161991639","data":{"timestamp":" 947161991639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161991892","data":{"timestamp":" 947161991892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161992618","data":{"timestamp":" 947161992617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161993442","data":{"timestamp":" 947161993441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161996138","data":{"timestamp":" 947161996137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161997138","data":{"timestamp":" 947161997138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161997616","data":{"timestamp":" 947161997615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161997887","data":{"timestamp":" 947161997886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161998677","data":{"timestamp":" 947161998676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947161999979","data":{"timestamp":" 947161999978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162000314","data":{"timestamp":" 947162000313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162001556","data":{"timestamp":" 947162001556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162002476","data":{"timestamp":" 947162002476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162003139","data":{"timestamp":" 947162003139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162003394","data":{"timestamp":" 947162003393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162004251","data":{"timestamp":" 947162004250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162004786","data":{"timestamp":" 947162004786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162005371","data":{"timestamp":" 947162005371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162005948","data":{"timestamp":" 947162005946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162008730","data":{"timestamp":" 947162008729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162009995","data":{"timestamp":" 947162009994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162011015","data":{"timestamp":" 947162011014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162012381","data":{"timestamp":" 947162012380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162013432","data":{"timestamp":" 947162013432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162013975","data":{"timestamp":" 947162013975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162015137","data":{"timestamp":" 947162015137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162016594","data":{"timestamp":" 947162016593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162017735","data":{"timestamp":" 947162017735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162018283","data":{"timestamp":" 947162018283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162019243","data":{"timestamp":" 947162019243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162021833","data":{"timestamp":" 947162021832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162022822","data":{"timestamp":" 947162022819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162023134","data":{"timestamp":" 947162023133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162023902","data":{"timestamp":" 947162023901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162025271","data":{"timestamp":" 947162025270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162025943","data":{"timestamp":" 947162025943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162026374","data":{"timestamp":" 947162026373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162027233","data":{"timestamp":" 947162027232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162028277","data":{"timestamp":" 947162028277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162028762","data":{"timestamp":" 947162028762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162029721","data":{"timestamp":" 947162029721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162029921","data":{"timestamp":" 947162029921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162030703","data":{"timestamp":" 947162030703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162033329","data":{"timestamp":" 947162033328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162034341","data":{"timestamp":" 947162034340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162035310","data":{"timestamp":" 947162035310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162036542","data":{"timestamp":" 947162036541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162037177","data":{"timestamp":" 947162037177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162038325","data":{"timestamp":" 947162038325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162039161","data":{"timestamp":" 947162039161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162039908","data":{"timestamp":" 947162039908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162040078","data":{"timestamp":" 947162040078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162040847","data":{"timestamp":" 947162040846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162044085","data":{"timestamp":" 947162044084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162045376","data":{"timestamp":" 947162045375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162046221","data":{"timestamp":" 947162046220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162048423","data":{"timestamp":" 947162048423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162049307","data":{"timestamp":" 947162049306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162050539","data":{"timestamp":" 947162050539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162051225","data":{"timestamp":" 947162051225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162051789","data":{"timestamp":" 947162051789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162052433","data":{"timestamp":" 947162052432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162053464","data":{"timestamp":" 947162053463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162053864","data":{"timestamp":" 947162053864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162054598","data":{"timestamp":" 947162054597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162055098","data":{"timestamp":" 947162055097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162055557","data":{"timestamp":" 947162055556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162056175","data":{"timestamp":" 947162056174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162058569","data":{"timestamp":" 947162058568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162060253","data":{"timestamp":" 947162060253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162061413","data":{"timestamp":" 947162061412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162062192","data":{"timestamp":" 947162062191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162062671","data":{"timestamp":" 947162062670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162063751","data":{"timestamp":" 947162063751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162064324","data":{"timestamp":" 947162064323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162066972","data":{"timestamp":" 947162066972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162067885","data":{"timestamp":" 947162067884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162068605","data":{"timestamp":" 947162068605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162068793","data":{"timestamp":" 947162068792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162069321","data":{"timestamp":" 947162069321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162070058","data":{"timestamp":" 947162070058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162070624","data":{"timestamp":" 947162070623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162073566","data":{"timestamp":" 947162073566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162074198","data":{"timestamp":" 947162074197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162077508","data":{"timestamp":" 947162077507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162078909","data":{"timestamp":" 947162078909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162079197","data":{"timestamp":" 947162079196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162080072","data":{"timestamp":" 947162080071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162081347","data":{"timestamp":" 947162081347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162082234","data":{"timestamp":" 947162082234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162082336","data":{"timestamp":" 947162082335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162082686","data":{"timestamp":" 947162082685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162083748","data":{"timestamp":" 947162083748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162084698","data":{"timestamp":" 947162084698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162086695","data":{"timestamp":" 947162086693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162087548","data":{"timestamp":" 947162087547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162087654","data":{"timestamp":" 947162087654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162088648","data":{"timestamp":" 947162088648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162090123","data":{"timestamp":" 947162090122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162091186","data":{"timestamp":" 947162091186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162092749","data":{"timestamp":" 947162092749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162093309","data":{"timestamp":" 947162093308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162094066","data":{"timestamp":" 947162094066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162097064","data":{"timestamp":" 947162097064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162098305","data":{"timestamp":" 947162098305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162099115","data":{"timestamp":" 947162099114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162100221","data":{"timestamp":" 947162100221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162100823","data":{"timestamp":" 947162100822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162101804","data":{"timestamp":" 947162101803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162102661","data":{"timestamp":" 947162102660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162103784","data":{"timestamp":" 947162103783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162104886","data":{"timestamp":" 947162104885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162107608","data":{"timestamp":" 947162107607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162108629","data":{"timestamp":" 947162108628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162110332","data":{"timestamp":" 947162110331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162110968","data":{"timestamp":" 947162110968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162111381","data":{"timestamp":" 947162111380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162112211","data":{"timestamp":" 947162112211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162115057","data":{"timestamp":" 947162115056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162116247","data":{"timestamp":" 947162116246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162116859","data":{"timestamp":" 947162116858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162117711","data":{"timestamp":" 947162117710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162118997","data":{"timestamp":" 947162118996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162119861","data":{"timestamp":" 947162119861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162120977","data":{"timestamp":" 947162120977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162121451","data":{"timestamp":" 947162121451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162122048","data":{"timestamp":" 947162122048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162122923","data":{"timestamp":" 947162122923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162123576","data":{"timestamp":" 947162123575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162124240","data":{"timestamp":" 947162124240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162124760","data":{"timestamp":" 947162124759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162125511","data":{"timestamp":" 947162125509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162125990","data":{"timestamp":" 947162125990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162126524","data":{"timestamp":" 947162126524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162127523","data":{"timestamp":" 947162127523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162127801","data":{"timestamp":" 947162127800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162128686","data":{"timestamp":" 947162128685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162130829","data":{"timestamp":" 947162130828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162131692","data":{"timestamp":" 947162131691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162132624","data":{"timestamp":" 947162132624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162133250","data":{"timestamp":" 947162133249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162133480","data":{"timestamp":" 947162133480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162134422","data":{"timestamp":" 947162134421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162135577","data":{"timestamp":" 947162135576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162136132","data":{"timestamp":" 947162136131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162136937","data":{"timestamp":" 947162136936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162137732","data":{"timestamp":" 947162137731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162138319","data":{"timestamp":" 947162138318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162139168","data":{"timestamp":" 947162139167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162140047","data":{"timestamp":" 947162140047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162140902","data":{"timestamp":" 947162140902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162141615","data":{"timestamp":" 947162141615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162143667","data":{"timestamp":" 947162143665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162144215","data":{"timestamp":" 947162144214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162145209","data":{"timestamp":" 947162145209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162145898","data":{"timestamp":" 947162145898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162149229","data":{"timestamp":" 947162149228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162150608","data":{"timestamp":" 947162150607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162150860","data":{"timestamp":" 947162150859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162151259","data":{"timestamp":" 947162151258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162152104","data":{"timestamp":" 947162152103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162153438","data":{"timestamp":" 947162153437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162155064","data":{"timestamp":" 947162155063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162155313","data":{"timestamp":" 947162155312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162156380","data":{"timestamp":" 947162156380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162157974","data":{"timestamp":" 947162157973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162159480","data":{"timestamp":" 947162159480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162160271","data":{"timestamp":" 947162160271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162160389","data":{"timestamp":" 947162160389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162161061","data":{"timestamp":" 947162161061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162161954","data":{"timestamp":" 947162161953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162164001","data":{"timestamp":" 947162164000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162164248","data":{"timestamp":" 947162164247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162164989","data":{"timestamp":" 947162164988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162165900","data":{"timestamp":" 947162165900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162166123","data":{"timestamp":" 947162166123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162167369","data":{"timestamp":" 947162167369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162169808","data":{"timestamp":" 947162169808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162170224","data":{"timestamp":" 947162170223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162170925","data":{"timestamp":" 947162170925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162171846","data":{"timestamp":" 947162171845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162172874","data":{"timestamp":" 947162172873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162174077","data":{"timestamp":" 947162174076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162174757","data":{"timestamp":" 947162174756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162175953","data":{"timestamp":" 947162175952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162176601","data":{"timestamp":" 947162176601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162177430","data":{"timestamp":" 947162177429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162177591","data":{"timestamp":" 947162177590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162178621","data":{"timestamp":" 947162178621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162180918","data":{"timestamp":" 947162180918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162181436","data":{"timestamp":" 947162181435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162182266","data":{"timestamp":" 947162182266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162185281","data":{"timestamp":" 947162185280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162185993","data":{"timestamp":" 947162185993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162186609","data":{"timestamp":" 947162186609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162187471","data":{"timestamp":" 947162187471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162188515","data":{"timestamp":" 947162188514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162190714","data":{"timestamp":" 947162190713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162191163","data":{"timestamp":" 947162191163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162192167","data":{"timestamp":" 947162192166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162193323","data":{"timestamp":" 947162193323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162194479","data":{"timestamp":" 947162194478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162195271","data":{"timestamp":" 947162195269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162196774","data":{"timestamp":" 947162196774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162197708","data":{"timestamp":" 947162197707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162199043","data":{"timestamp":" 947162199043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162199573","data":{"timestamp":" 947162199572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162200195","data":{"timestamp":" 947162200194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162201059","data":{"timestamp":" 947162201058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162201895","data":{"timestamp":" 947162201893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162202534","data":{"timestamp":" 947162202533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162203095","data":{"timestamp":" 947162203094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162203284","data":{"timestamp":" 947162203283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947162203380","data":{"timestamp":" 947162203380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_142147"," gameId":" 9095e7c1-5d98-42d4-b3df-38880f981414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}